- [EKG BEEPING]
- [VENTILATOR WHOOSHING]
[SNIFFLES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
[MAN SPEAKING IN JAPANESE ON TV]
The boomslang was stolen
from the zoo last night.
It's extremely dangerous.
[IN JAPANESE] Father.
[IN JAPANESE] Any news on my grandson?
No change.
He hasn't woken up.
A father's job is to protect his family.
When Wataru was on that roof...
when he was pushed...
where was his father?
Wataru is lucky.
You never know what horrible fate
your bad luck has saved you from.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
["STAYIN' ALIVE" PLAYING]
[MAN SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ Stayin' alive, stayin' alive ♪
♪ Stayin' alive, stayin' alive... ♪
MARIA: Thank you for taking the job
on such short notice.
I am ready.
You are getting the new and improved me.
Since I've been working with Barry,
I am experiencing a calm
like never before. Never.
Like, I'm less reactive to situations,
I'm more accepting
of people's shortcomings.
I was a little uncertain about coming
back to work, but it's like Barry says:
You put peace out in the world,
you get peace back.
I think your new therapist
might be forgetting
what you do for a living, little Ladybug.
- Ladybug?
- Mm-hm. Your new operational name.
- Ladybug? Really?
- You don't like it?
- Do you like it?
- I like it.
Well, if you like it, all right.
Oh, I see what you're doing.
Ladybugs are supposed to be lucky.
- Ha, ha,
- [HORN HONKS]
[GROANS]
- You don't have bad luck.
- Really?
My bad luck is biblical. I'm not even
trying to kill people and someone dies.
That's an exaggeration.
LADYBUG: it is? My last job?
- The political blackmail photos?
- [MOANS] I voted for you.
Remember the suicidal bellboy
climbed the roof of his hotel,
couldn't take it anymore?
[YELLING]
MARIA:
Seems more like his bad luck than yours.
[GROANING]
Hang in there, buddy!
MARIA: And he didn't die.
Okay? You drove him to the hospital.
It's good luck.
- All in how you frame it.
- Sure.
Gotta say I like it here.
I could live here.
I like the atmosphere,
the people are considerate...
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Except for that guy.
Why is this job paying so well?
It was supposed to be Carver's,
but he's got some stomach thing.
- Carver?
- And he doesn't do snatch-and-grabs.
I'm filling in for Carver?
You picked me second to Carver?
You said you wanted simple
for your first job back.
Doesn't get simpler.
- Shit.
- Shit what?
I think I must have lost the key
when that guy bumped into me.
- What's the number again?
- 523.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Carver.
What an ego.
I mean, talk about
a candidate for self-improvement.
Calling in sick?
I mean, what is that, high school?
Mm. I can hear that personal growth.
I know I'm being judgmental.
I need to work on that.
But, Jesus, what a douchebag.
You have the strangest requests.
Firecrackers?
I'm industrious.
Please tell me
you didn't order the sleeping powder.
Nope.
You almost gave that bodyguard
in Anchorage a heart attack.
I've worked on the dosage.
Take the gun.
[IN JAPANESE] Ticket please.
Thank you for using our train.
First class is that way.
[SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
MARIA:
I'll assume you didn't take the gun?
Barry says every conflict
is an opportunity for a peaceful...
What was it?
And your handler says
some conflicts require a gun.
Shit.
[TRAIN ALERT CHIMING]
Okay, I'm on.
Well, that's a start.
Hey, this is nice.
Economy?
I'm thinking of starting my own agency.
You know, all simple jobs, all the time.
That's a terrible business plan.
No more sociopaths, no more maniacs.
Just quality people.
Barry says it's time for some change.
I think he's right.
Barry does not know
what you do for a living.
Okay, here we go.
The bullet train has 16 cars.
Ten economy, six first-class,
and remember,
only one minute stop at every station.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- Bloody fuckin' hell. Do you mind?
- [BOTH SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
What is he, fucking blind or something?
Come on. No, you don't
have to nick the biscuits, man.
[SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
Oh, no. You all right? Okay, cool.
- Fucking asshole.
- Thank you.
Why'd I do that?
It's like I got a compulsion or something.
I have to take it if I see it.
Need to talk to someone. Serious.
A goldfish biscuit?
I mean, I don't understand it.
Okay, simple snatch-and-grab.
What am I snatching and/or grabbing?
A briefcase. Intel says
there's a train sticker on the handle.
Briefcases have owners.
Owners are not simple.
And the last update says
the owners will be in economy class.
Owners, plural?
Why didn't you tell me to bring that gun?
I did.
You chose spiritual enlightenment.
Chiketto, please.
Ticket.
Hold on.
[IN ENGLISH] Ah, no, no. Receipt.
Oh. Uh...
Shit, I think I dropped my ticket, too.
Uh, that receipt shows
I bought a ticket, though, right?
One stop.
Yep.
[SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
[IN ENGLISH] I thought they bowed here.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
I PUSHED HIM. FIRST CLASS, SEAT B4
[GASPS]
[IN JAPANESE] Sorry, kid.
I'm looking for...
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS WEAKLY]
[IN ENGLISH] You found her.
- Oh, Lemon.
- Tangerine.
You're bleeding, mate.
Oh, mate, shit. Oh, shit, man.
Who the fuck did I kill?
- Get a Wet One on it or something.
- It's not mine, mate.
- Oh, it's not yours?
- Yeah. I don't bleed.
In that case, leave your jacket open,
let everyone have a good old look.
- Yeah, I want everyone to see my tie.
- Fuck is wrong with you?
Pull your coat together
so no one else notices, Lemon.
I think they'll notice
the childish code names first.
But if we're gonna stick with fruit,
why not, uh, apple or orange?
So, what's in this case?
Are we doing this?
You know what's in the case.
Money. It's always money.
Tangerines are sophisticated.
Now he's callin' a fruit sophisticated.
Yeah, it's cross-hybridized
with other fruit.
They're adaptable. [SNIFFS] Like me.
LADYBUG: You said six cars in economy,
say 30 passengers per car,
guessing two bags per,
let's see, uh, times two and you carry--
Yeah, no fuckin' way
I'm gonna find one brie--
- Wait.
- What?
- Train sticker on the handle?
- Yeah.
Holy shitbox.
- And why am I Lemon?
- TANGERINE: Because you're sour.
- No one likes lemons.
- That's bollocks, mate.
Lemonades, lemon drops.
- You got a sore throat?
- Lemon meringue pie.
When's the last time
you ate a lemon meringue pie?
- Lemon drizzle cake.
- I'm sorry, are you talking about lemons?
- I have the case.
- MARIA: Well, that's great.
- Is it?
- Yes.
- What's the catch?
- There is a no catch.
- There's always a catch.
- Get off the train.
Quite like lemons. I just hate code names.
Oh, well, look at this. Sleeping Beauty.
- Wakey, wakey.
- LEMON: Eggs and bakey.
Where am I?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're safe now. Your father sent us.
You idiots work for my father?
Ooh, easy, we could deliver you
back to your pops in a box.
Technically, we're outside contractors.
I'm Tangerine. He's Lemon.
Like the fruit?
- You ever watch Thomas the Tank Engine?
- Here we go.
Hey, you watch something nowadays,
what is it, huh? Nothing.
It's twists, violence, drama, no message.
What's the point? Huh?
What are we supposed to learn?
Everything I learned about people
I learned from Thomas.
- You bring your sticker book, did ya?
- You know I always bring my stickers.
Take Tangerine here.
He's a Gordon. This blue one.
And Gordon is the strongest,
the most important.
But he doesn't always listen to others.
What's that, now?
I mean, some people are Edwards.
Wise, kind.
Some are Henrys.
Hard-working, strong.
Some people are Diesels.
Fuck me!
Those are trouble.
You, though...
Yeah, you seem like a Percy.
Young.
Sweet.
Not all there.
[LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY]
You finished, both of you?
- Yeah.
- Right. Your daddy
hired us to get you out of the trouble
you got yourself into, naughty boy.
- Why are you Tangerine, though?
- Oh, it's sophisticated, mate.
Oh, fuckin' hell.
It's not important, is it?
What is important
are the 17 dead bodies we left
getting you back from the Triad
that kidnapped you
with the plans to ransom you to your
extremely psychotic fucked-up father.
Actually, it's 16.
What's that, now?
- Sixteen kills, mate.
- No, it was 17.
- It's 16.
- Seven.
You're startin' to get on my fucking tits.
- Sixteen.
- I'll smash my fucking head
- through a brick wall.
- Maybe that'd help your memory
'cause it was 16.
It was 17, goddamn it.
I wanna fucking strangle you now.
Do you mind if we do this right now?
- [ARGUING INDISTINCTLY]
- ["I'M FOREVER BLOWING BUBBLES" PLAYING]
♪ I'm forever blowing bubbles ♪
One.
♪ Pretty bubbles in the air ♪
Two, three.
♪ They fly so high
Nearly reach the sky ♪
Five guys playing poker.
♪ Then like my dreams
They fade and die ♪
♪ Fortune's always hiding ♪
♪ I've looked everywhere... ♪
LEMON: Keep moving!
- Big guy.
- Yeah, big guy.
Sometime today!
♪ Pretty bubbles ♪
Ten.
♪ In the air ♪
Three assholes with swords.
[ALL YELL]
Fucking get it. Fuck!
Why do you always bring swords?
Fucking Triad. You would, wouldn't ya?
You son of a bitch!
I like swords, actually.
[ENGINES REVVING]
Looks like it's time for a Jaffa Cake.
How about a Wagon Wheel?
Oh, that works.
TANGERINE: Swing!
♪ I've looked everywhere ♪
Fourteen, fifteen.
♪ I'm forever blowing bubbles ♪
And the prick on the motorcycle.
♪ Pretty bubbles in the air ♪
- So 16.
- You forgot the poor,
- innocent civilian on the street.
- The fuck you--?
Hey, buddy.
Hey, buddy, you okay? Oh, my--
Shit. That wasn't our fault.
- Wasn't our fault?
- No.
Well, what would
Thomas the Tank Engine say, Lemon?
That's really mean.
He'd say,
"Hey, take responsibility, mate."
- He doesn't sound like that.
- [IMITATES TRAIN WHISTLE]
Gonna put a little distance
between me and the owners.
- MARIA: Are you nervous?
- Yeah, I'm nervous.
- You sound nervous.
- Because I am, in fact, nervous.
Hey, listen,
I'm just gonna get off at the next stop.
Oh, let's have a seat, then, huh?
Do you know
what they call your papushka?
Course I fucking do.
The White Death. Not exactly a fruit.
No. There you go.
There's a story--
Stop me if you've heard it.
--Where this woman found herself
in the unfortunate position
of owing your father a tidy sum of money.
Now, the issue was it took her
some time to acquire this money.
But she did pay it back
five minutes late, didn't she?
- Yeah, what'd he do?
- Cut her arm off.
- Fuckin' hell!
- Yeah.
He said she owed him a finger
for every minute.
He's not a monster. He didn't
make her sit through it five times.
He just cut once, didn't he?
Ow!
- This is too easy.
- You're overthinking it.
- You're underthinking it.
- It's not a word.
- Yes, it is.
- Really?
I think it is.
- Did you Google it?
- Doesn't matter.
What would Barry say?
Barry would say, "A negative outlook
leads to a negative outcome."
Wow. How much do you pay him again?
Our job is to keep you safe
and to recover the briefcase
with the ransom money inside.
And I plan on completin' my job
and keeping...
Lemon. Where's the briefcase?
Oh, I stashed it.
The case, Lemon.
Go get me the fucking case.
[SIGHS] You're a liability, you know?
To my father.
Hm?
He doesn't need a reason
to kill people like you.
He needs a reason not to.
Does he have one?
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
That's fucking confusin'.
- Hello?
- MAN: Do you have White Death's son?
You mean this dickhead
with the silly face tattoos?
- He's sat right here.
- And the briefcase?
Yes, of course, I've got the case.
You will both deboard at Kyoto station.
Then your business with him
will be concluded.
[CALL DISCONNECTS]
[TRAIN ALERT CHIMES]
[WOMAN SPEAKING IN JAPANESE ON PA]
It was just here.
Well, it's not anymore.
We need to find
the person who took that case.
LADYBUG: Maybe you're right.
Maybe my luck is starting to turn.
["POWER" PLAYING ON HEADPHONES]
[GROANS]
♪ Unlocked my front door, I want more ♪
♪ Face down
My mouth on the fucking floor ♪
♪ Hurt me, I'll hurt back ♪
♪ Just like this, just like that... ♪
[IN JAPANESE] You.
Yes.
Me.
But you are Yuichi Kimura.
And you came here to kill me.
My parents call me malen'kiy prints.
That means little prince.
Obviously, they wanted a boy.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You're going to want
to hear the whole story.
Or you'll be very, very sorry.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
It's the hospital.
Hang on.
Hi. Yes, you can see the boy now.
Good. if you don't hear from me
every ten minutes
or if I don't answer this phone
when you call,
I want you to go in there and kill...
I'm sorry, what's your boy's name again?
Wataru.
Right. Right.
Kill Wataru.
Aren't we glad we waited?
We got his son. That was our job.
Our job was to come back
with his son and his $10 million.
Three words describe
our situation right now.
- Do you know what they are?
- Sure do. Saved... his... son. Hm?
Family's more important
than money, right?
Do you honestly not know
who the White Death is?
I know the White Death.
You just told me 5 minutes ago.
Why do I even bother
forwarding you the briefings?
I do not know.
[DRAMATIC ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
The Japanese underworld
used to be ruled by a man named Minegishi.
Now, Minegishi was one brutal bastard.
But he was old-school, you know?
Tradition and loyalty
was all that mattered to him.
When you were in, you were in.
You were like family.
He treated you
like you were one of his own.
Then out of the blue comes this
6-foot-fucking-6 geezer from Russia.
Whispers that he was exiled from the
Russian mafia or that he was ex-KGB.
No one really knows the truth.
But what is known is this Russian
worked his way up the ranks.
Bit by bit. Kill by kill.
And very, very fucking quickly became
one of Minegishi's closest advisors.
And those loyal to him said:
"Hold your horses.
This geezer ain't the full ticket.
He ain't to be trusted."
"He's dangerous," they said.
"A modern plague," they said.
"A White Death."
So, sure enough, they were right.
He made his own alliance.
His own gang.
And what'd he do?
Stabbed him in the back.
I mean, metaphorically.
He blew his fucking brains out, didn't he?
He wiped the name Minegishi off
the face of the earth in one single night.
And made an empire
worthy of the White Death.
So, let me put this bluntly.
There's this soulless psychotic leader
with the largest criminal organization
on the planet
shoved right inside
our fucking ass cheeks.
That motherfucker's
definitely a Diesel, then, isn't he?
If you mention Thomas the Tank Engine
one more time
- I'm gonna shoot you in the fucking face.
- Okay, if he's such a badass,
how come he hired two random operators
instead of getting his son back himself?
If you actually read the briefings
you'd know that he had a wife.
What, he had a wife?
She was the most important
fucking thing in his life, and she died.
Drunk driving accident or some shit.
And now he's at the compound.
He ain't left since.
An unnamed locomotive
might say there's a lesson to be learned.
And he didn't hire
two random operators, Lemon.
No, he asked for the best.
He asked for the two responsible
for the Bolivia job.
[CHAINSAW BUZZES]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
He asked for pros who wouldn't fuck up.
Three words, Lemon.
- We are--
- Fucked.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[IN ENGLISH] What do you want?
People think
that I'm just some young girl.
Someone's future wife...
or future mother.
But I'm not in someone else's story.
You're all in mine.
The fuck does that have to do with me?
You work for the most feared boss
in the city: The White Death.
Oh, deny it all you want.
But you work for someone who works
for someone else, et cetera, et cetera,
and it all falls under the same person.
You delivered a briefcase two days ago
to one of the White Death's associates,
and I saw my opportunity.
Follow the case and find the White Death.
I don't know
what you think I can do for you.
Oh, that is my favorite part of the story.
You're going to kill him for me.
How the fuck
am I going to kill the White Death?
You'll see.
Oh, look at that.
We are right on schedule.
Sit back, relax a little bit.
You look so tense.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
We rescued his fucking son. Huh?
We find the fucker who took the briefcase,
make things right,
be like it never happened.
You still got that vest on ya?
No, vests give you
a false sense of security.
You might, like, get shot in the neck.
It also stops you
from getting shot in the chest,
but I guess you missed
that episode of Thomas.
I really must've,
because that sounds dark as shit.
Nut up or shut up, bruv.
[PUNK ROCK "I'M FOREVER BLOWING BUBBLES" PLAYING]
♪ I'm forever blowing bubbles ♪
♪ Pretty bubbles in the air ♪
♪ They fly so high
They nearly reach the sky ♪
Well, so, slight change of plans.
- [SONG DISTORTS]
- Oh!
First his wife, now his son?
That's a lot of white deaths.
["LA DESPEDIDA" PLAYING]
[IN SPANISH] I want you to be strong, son.
Do you understand?
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Be strong.
[HOWLS]
[IN SPANISH] My heart.
[YELLS]
- [SONG ENDS]
- [WEDDING GUESTS SCREAMING]
No!
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Find me the son of a bitch who did this.
[SPANISH GUITAR BALLAD PLAYING]
You lucky son of a bitch.
You stabbed me?!
- [IN ENGLISH] You ruined my life.
- I don't even know you!
I come here for revenge.
The assassin who killed El Saguaro
killed my wife.
[IN SPANISH]
But fate made this a two for one special.
Can we just take a time-out here?
Talk this out?
[IN ENGLISH]
I will never stop coming for you.
What?
Run as far as you like.
I will find you.
Why?
And I will ruin your life
the way you ruined mine!
Dude, I don't even know you!
[IN SPANISH] My heart.
What the--?
Wow. Really?
Let this be a lesson
in the toxicity of anger.
Venezuela, Uruguay, Barcelona.
Who are you?
Mmm!
[TRAIN ALERT CHIMES]
[WOMAN SPEAKING IN JAPANESE OVER PA]
[IN ENGLISH] All passengers:
We'll make a brief stop
- at Shin Yokohama.
- LEMON: All right, mate, try these.
- They're them Momonga glasses.
- The fuck is a Momonga?
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Comes on after Thomas every Thursday.
- Okay.
- It's good.
- Just like that.
- He should look asleep. There, like that.
Ah!
Mmm!
Wasabi.
We gotta make sure
he doesn't step a foot off this train.
You see the case,
deal with whoever has it.
All right, how do I do that?
Talk to him, or, like, talk to him?
Why don't you tell him about the
story about how Gordon met Percy
and how Percy's now bleeding
from his fucking eye sockets!
He means kill him.
[WOMAN ON PA] All passengers:
- We'll make a brief stop at Shin Yokohama.
- Goddamn it.
Excuse me.
You are fuckin' excused.
Arigato.
[SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[IN ENGLISH] Joburg.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Give it!
[SQUEAKS]
Shitballs!
That wasn't a minute.
[PHONE BEEPS]
- I missed my stop.
- MARIA: Why?
- Because God hates me.
- No, she doesn't.
- Do you still have the case?
- Yeah, I stashed it.
- Get off at the next stop.
- It sounds so easy when you say it.
Does the name El Cigarillo
mean anything to you?
- El Saguaro? The cartel boss?
- Yeah, why does that sound so familiar?
He was in the wedding
you infiltrated in Mexico.
- Tequila?
- You were the cocktail server.
The groom.
I knew I recognized that guy.
- I'm really good with faces.
- Wait, what guy?
Sorry. Be right back.
The guy who stabbed me.
I spilled wine on his suit. He's dead now.
- You killed the Wolf?
- It was an accident.
I'm really gonna have to process
my part in the incident on Monday.
Shit! Fuck! No.
Shit. Fuck. What?
Remember those two wackos from the
Bolivia job killed all those people?
- The Twins?
- Yeah, I'm not so sure they're twins.
Stop it. Everyone knows they're twins.
One of them is walking
towards me right now.
I think I saw the other
one on the platform.
[WOMAN IN JAPANESE] Occupied.
Now we know
who the owners of the case are.
This is exactly what I'm talkin' about.
We have to have a hard discussion
about the caliber of people
- we are surrounding ourselves with.
- Why are we whispering?
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
- Hello.
- MAN: The White Death would like to know
- why you stepped off train.
- Wanted some fresh air.
Your orders were to stay on the train.
I didn't realize I was gettin'
a babysitter to come cut my bollocks.
I'm a professional. We're making sure
the case and his son are perfectly safe.
- Can I please go do my job now?
- If something is go wrong...
Oh, very kind of you.
Thank you very much.
Fuck me! Jesus Christ.
It's very rude, talking on the phone,
on the train in Japan.
This rude enough for ya,
ya fucking prick?
Shove that fuckin' hat
up your fuckin' asshole, you hear me?
Fuck this job.
I knew we should have got an upgrade,
fuck all.
I beg your pardon, sorry.
I wasn't aware
there was a young lady present. Apologize.
You didn't happen to see someone come by
with a silver briefcase, did ya?
There's a little train sticker
by the handle.
Actually, yeah.
A man with black framed glasses had it.
He went that way.
Thank you, love.
That fucking bastard.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
LEMON:
"Guy in black glasses. Stop him."
- Hi. There's a gun under this table--
- LEMON: Shh.
This is the quiet car. Gotta use
your small inside voice in here, son.
There's a gun underneath this table
pointed right at you, so I would--
- I can't really hear what you're saying.
- There's a gun--
- [SHUSHING]
- [CHUCKLES]
I'm just fuckin' with you, mate.
It's been a long time
since Johannesburg.
Yeah. Who the fuck are you?
Really. You don't remember me?
You look like every white homeless man
I've ever seen.
Okay.
Well, I have something
I believe you're looking f--
- Really? You don't remember me?
- I remember Johannesburg,
- but I don't remember you.
- You shot me.
- I shoot a lot of people.
- You shot me twice.
Ow!
Well, you also have a shootable face.
I know you're Black Framed Glasses.
The cheeky fucker
who took our briefcase.
Yes. Yes, I am.
Hm.
You know, I've done a lot
of personal work since Joburg.
I've forgiven, I've moved on.
I've learned that
with any potential conflict
there's an opportunity for growth,
a path to a peaceful outcome.
PRINCE: Interesting.
Who is that?
I have no idea.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
How did you know that was there?
Didn't I mention?
I've always been lucky.
It was then that I took
a long, hard look into the mirror.
And you know what?
Buddy, I didn't like what I saw.
Nope. Nada.
LEMON: Hm.
- Until I did. You know?
- Mm.
- Between us now sits a wall.
- Mm-hm.
But it's an illusion.
For within every wall,
uh, awaits a window--
Oh, wait, it's a door.
Real quick, um, every day
is a fucking headache with you, innit?
Right. You and your partner--
I'm Lemon, he's Tangerine.
Okay, Lemon-- Like the fruit?
Blessings.
Mm.
- What's your plan here?
- Here's the plan.
I give you back your case,
you don't kill me.
You give your case to your employer,
he doesn't kill you.
You're alive, I'm alive,
everyone's happy.
Win-win, don't you think?
How do you know whoever hired you
won't kill you for failing your job?
Lose-lose. No happy.
Man, I just wanna get off this train,
go see a Zen garden
and some shit, you know?
- I'd like to accept your offer.
- Great.
But then you went and killed someone.
Didn't you?
- How did you know...?
- Wasn't exactly subtle.
It was an accident. Tragic.
Bizarre, even.
Cool story, bro,
but I think you had your own plans
of getting out of here with that case.
- No, no.
- Pinning a body on us.
Hoping the White Death
is so busy cuttin' off our arms
instead of cuttin' off our fingers.
It's like Thomas the Tank Engine
always says: "Simple is better."
- The kids' show?
- Yes, the fucking ki-- Man.
I learned everything
about people from Thomas.
- Everything.
- Really?
It's how I can read people like you
so well.
- And you are a Diesel.
- I am not a Diesel.
- You're the Diesel-est Diesel...
- Not even close.
...I've ever seen in my life, man.
'Cause Diesels bluff. They go too far.
I'm trying to get Diesels
out of my life, you know?
If there was a gun under this table, yeah,
I'd be as dead as that kid over there.
Hm?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SHUSHING]
[GRUNTING CONTINUES]
- Uh-uh.
- Mm-hm.
Nope.
You mother--
Have the courage to listen.
- [SHUSHING]
- [LADYBUG HUMMING]
[GRUNTING CONTINUES]
Come on, Joburg.
No.
Shot number three.
No, no, no. I ain't got the time
or the patience, let alone the interest.
- Fucking hell.
- [MASCOT SQUEAKING]
Are you following me? Stop!
&$#%*
- Asshole!
- Ow!
[GRUNTING CONTINUES]
Shh! [WHISPERS] I'll call the conductor!
[WHISPERS] Eat a bag of dicks, lady!
- [WOMAN GASPS]
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm working on it.
I'm not a Diesel, you're a Diesel.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Ow!
- PASSENGER: Shh!
- There's another body here.
- MARIA: Of course there is.
Not my fault, and I believe
it's the son of the White Death.
Did the Twins ID you?
Did you hear what I said?
White Death. Death. Death.
Snatch-and-grab, my ass.
There's someone else
doing a job on this train.
The Twins. We know that.
Again, not twins.
Loonies, but not twins.
They're here for the kid,
but somebody killed the kid.
- The guy with the knife.
- The Wolf.
[HOWLS]
He said he came here for revenge.
He just happened to run into me,
because of course he did.
Now, get this.
The kid was poisoned in the same way
as El Sbarro was at the wedding.
It's El Saguaro.
- The same killer?
- Yeah.
I'm like MacGyver.
Fuck!
[NEWS FANFARE PLAYING]
[IN JAPANESE] All of Japan is in terror
because a poisonous snake was stolen.
HANDLER: Boomslang snakes
have a very strong poison.
When they bite,
it can cause internal bleeding...
and bleeding from holes in the body.
Oh, shit.
MARIA: What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Fuck this, man.
Fuck Carver.
Shit.
- Oh, thank God. For a minute there...
- [GROANS]
Jesus Christ,
you had a bit of a bosh, pal.
All right. Five stations to Kyoto.
Better get tickety-boo.
Would you describe me
as someone who lives in perpetual anxiety?
No, no.
Ah, fucknuts.
And if it wasn't clear, I meant "yes."
- The conductor, I don't have a ticket.
- Not sure that's your biggest concern.
You don't understand,
this guy's like Criss-fuckin'-Angel.
He pops up everywhere.
He slows me down,
Tangerine catches me, I am dead.
Dead. Dead.
Hold on.
Hey, bro.
Wanna make an easy 200 bucks?
Is this like a... sex thing?
Nope.
Oh, okay. I was kidding.
Uh, yeah, what's up?
What do you need, bro?
[TOY SQUEAKS]
All right, game's up, big boy.
Where is the case?
Tell me, and I promise
I'll only shoot you enough--
Whoa, whoa, um, is this the sex stuff?
[FIRECRACKERS EXPLODING]
Twat!
- Shit.
- I do love an accent.
[PASSENGERS CHATTERING]
Come on.
Oops.
Picture it.
Picture what?
Well, the man. Watching your son.
I wonder how he'll do it.
Maybe a pillow to the face.
Or maybe something clever.
Like an air bubble in the IV.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
No, no. You hold onto it.
The innocent young girl act
doesn't really get you very far
if you're holding a loaded gun.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Put it on speaker.
- [IN JAPANESE] Father.
- Yuichi?
Why did you leave the hospital?
Be honest.
Who's there with you?
I found out who pushed Wataru
off that roof.
Did you go to the authorities?
I wanted to handle it myself.
My son.
You can't control
what fate has in store for us.
Father.
I'm sorry.
We're not finished.
You're going to sit here and you're going
to go through every combination
until you open up that case.
- [IN ENGLISH] Kid, that could take f--
- No, no. It won't.
I'd start with the low numbers.
Just a thought.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS] Fuck me!
- There he is.
- He got by me.
Yeah. Yeah, me, too.
I guess our best option now
is, uh, bring the White Death
the man who killed his son.
- But Glasses didn't do it.
- I could give a rat's ass.
No, I'm telling you, I read him.
He's not the type, mate.
I'll tell you what, do you like your arms?
- You know I like my arms.
- Well, then
someone's got to take the blame,
don't they?
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
- That's you or me?
- You or me?
Shit, that asshole stole my phone.
And my gun, Lucille.
- Oh, come on.
- That's my favorite gun. Son of a bitch.
Fuck about.
- Right, what?
- MAN: Step off the train at the next stop
- with the briefcase and the son.
- Hang on a minute, didn't we say Kyoto?
You will still depart at Kyoto.
The White Death wants to make sure
you are being honest about situation.
- Well, this is a complete waste of our t--
- [CALL DISCONNECTS]
All right, all right. We just have
to prove we have a case we don't have
and a live son instead of a dead one.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you thinking?
- The ol' Punch and Judy?
- The ol' Punch and Judy.
["KILL ME PRETTY" PLAYING]
You were all told to exit the train.
Yeah? Well, unlike you,
I'm a professional.
I wanted to make sure it weren't
some Yakuza trap, but clearly not.
It's some fuckin' '80s dance-off, innit?
Where is your twin? Tangerine?
I'm Tangerine.
Lemon's keepin' the case safe.
And the White Death's son?
Yeah, he's there.
Wave to your fuckin' fans, princess.
He's a fuckin' happy chappy, isn't he?
But, uh, I've gotta pop on the train,
you know, ten seconds left, so ta-ra.
We'll stick to the plan,
depart in Kyoto.
Do us a favor:
Get the fuck off my back, will ya?
Okay.
Whoa!
- That couldn't have gone better.
- Yeah, let's hope they buy it.
We need to find that Glasses twat,
like, right to the fuck now.
[GROANS] I'm gonna go up, you go down,
double back when you're done.
If you see him,
fucking deal with him, yeah?
Yeah.
- Up is...?
- That way. Towards Tokyo.
Departing trains
are always moving down.
And, look, be careful.
- Something else is going on here.
- Yeah?
Yeah, I still feel like
there's a Diesel lurking about.
I swear to God, what did I say?
What did I say?
- I said I'll fucking--
- Shoot me in the face. Yeah.
Thomas still taught me how to see people,
read them for real.
Yeah.
- And I'm never wrong, am I?
- No.
Glasses, he is not our guy.
Okay.
You shoot first
and come up with the answers later.
I always do.
And, Lemon?
Yeah, man?
You be careful, too.
I mean, when this train's a-rockin'
don't come a-knockin', right?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[JAPANESE ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING]
LADYBUG: Seven more minutes
and I am off this train.
MARIA: Are you hiding in the bathroom?
Yeah. Have you tried
these smart toilets?
They're a pleasure to the senses.
If I had one in the chamber
I would rock this bad boy right now.
Boundaries. We need boundaries.
[KIMURA MUMBLING]
[LOCK CLICKS]
Holy shit.
Whoa there.
Oh, look at that.
I knew my luck would rub off on you.
Fuck.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What the fuck are you doing?
I am doing the same thing
that I did to the gun in your hand.
I'm just making things interesting.
I'm hedging my bets, you could say.
Fuck.
If the gun doesn't kill him,
the case will.
This thing could have
blown up in my hand at any point.
No, no. It's inert unless you fire it.
But don't fire it,
you know what I mean?
Unlike what I put in this briefcase here.
This is very...
Well, this is not inert at all.
This is...
[KIMURA GROANS]
Did you know that there have been
31 attempts on the White Death's life
from within his own organization?
Each one,
he executed with their own weapon.
Do you see what I'm getting at here?
Kimura, I brought you here to fail.
You push my son off a roof...
- Right.
- ...bring me to this train...
frame me as an assassin
here to kill the White Death,
and use my gun...
that will blow up in his face?
Very good.
Very, very good.
It's a stupid plan.
It is...
a brilliant plan.
- [CHIMES]
- [WOMAN SPEAKS IN JAPANESE ON RECORDING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Occupied.
MARIA: You remember that mob surgeon
that died mid-heart operation?
- Yeah, he had a stroke, right?
- No, that was the official cover.
He was poisoned. The assassin
goes by the name of the Hornet.
[SCREAMING] Oh, my God!
MARIA: He used boomslang snake venom.
It congeals the blood,
making you bleed out of every orifice.
If the antidote isn't administered
within 30 seconds, you're dead.
Fun fact:
The same poison that was used on--
El Sagardo.
MARIA: It's El Saguaro.
What is the Hornet doing on this train?
Well, whatever deal was made, it wasn't
done through the normal channels.
There's something else going on here.
[WOMAN IN JAPANESE]
How long are you going to be?
It's still occupied, lady.
&$#%*
The Wolf must have
figured out who the Hornet is,
came here for revenge for his wife,
his boss, came here to whack the Hornet.
Oh, my God, did you just say "whack"?
- I did, I'm bringing it back.
- No, it needs to stay where it was.
If I can figure out who the Hornet is,
I can give him to Lemon and Tangerine
so they don't whack me.
- Really?
- You see what I did there?
You're really proud of yourself,
aren't you?
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Jeez, they're usually so polite here.
Lady, I'm so--
[BEEPING]
Oh. That's cool.
Bastard!
[LIVELY ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Come here, you dirty fucking scum!
Wait, wait, wait.
I know who killed the kid.
I couldn't give a rat's ass.
Where's my fucking case?
[MUSIC STOPS]
[SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
Yeah.
Oh.
- [SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
- Oh, I'm so sorry. Excuse me.
- Oh, no, thank you. We're okay.
Oh, I would love a bottle of water.
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
You know what? Do you have
anything sparkling? With bubbles?
That's the one. Thank--
[BOTH SPEAK IN JAPANESE]
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Bro, I just remembered I gave all my money
to that guy to wear my hat and glasses.
Could you?
How much for the bottle of water, love?
- [SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
- LADYBUG: Ah!
Oh, there. No, you're welcome. Yeah.
A thousand yen. That's ten quid
for that bottle of water, mate.
LADYBUG: Mmm.
- [SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
- Ta-ra.
[SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
[IN ENGLISH]
You sure you don't wanna talk this out?
Not particularly, no.
Okay.
[LIVELY ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
You fucking bastard!
Fucker! Come here, you little fuck!
I know who killed the kid.
Yeah? Where the fuck is he, then?
He's on this train.
Well, that narrows it down,
then, don't it?
Let go! Get off!
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
You gonna get that?
No.
You probably oughta get that.
It could be important.
Okay, maybe it's important.
Fucking hell. Come here.
Yeah, what do you want?
The White Death says to get off
at next stop holding the briefcase
or he will kill everyone on that train.
Okay, yeah, I can make it, but Lemon,
he's a little tied up right now.
Both of you this time. With the case.
Or everyone dies.
Fuckin' paranoid, this lot.
You don't happen to have the case
on you, do ya?
No.
Yeah, I don't think
I'd reach Lemon in time anyway.
You still got his phone.
Do you have a gun on ya?
- Don't like 'em.
- Well...
Game's up, mate.
For what it's worth,
you seem like a right fucking asshole
and I'm glad
you're gonna fucking die with me.
That's nice.
[GROANS]
- Just curious.
- Yeah?
Do they even know
what Lemon looks like?
Wow.
You two do look like twins, huh?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah, okay. We got the case, now what?
You still take the train to Kyoto Station.
Mm-hm. Yeah. Okay.
We can do that. Wonderful.
GUNHAND: Hey.
- Have you opened the case?
- TANGERINE: No, of course not.
I never asked for the combination,
you know what I mean?
Keep it safe that way.
[LADYBUG IN BRITISH ACCENT] Yeah.
So no one gets greedy.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] I know, I know.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- I have this bad luck thing.
- Is that what you call it?
I hit the thing and it went:
- Why did you even bother trying?
- I was trying to sell it.
Well, I don't think
they were in the market
for fucking dildos and pantyhose,
were they?
But they were buying it.
I had 'em.
KIMURA: You proved you're smarter
than everyone. You've won, kid.
Please.
Please, kid.
Call your man.
I'll do what you want.
Just leave my son alone.
Your son.
Do you know how easy it was
to get him to follow me up onto that roof?
Didn't think
it would take you three hours
to even realize your son was missing.
You're a terrible father,
and your son is going to pay
for all the mistakes that you've made.
You don't know anything about life.
How hard it is.
You're just...
some spoiled girl
who breaks their toys
when Mommy says she has to pick up.
Sorry. Pardon me, I don't mean
to interrupt what's, uh, going on here.
But you wouldn't happen to have seen
a tiny white prick with a pair of glasses
come through here, have you?
No.
What about a silver case with a train
sticker by the handle? You seen that?
It's not ringing any--
Uncle Kimura, have you seen
a silver briefcase with the train--
Did you say
"train sticker by the handle"?
- The handle had a train sticker.
- That's unique.
No, I haven't seen anything like that.
I think I'd remember.
LEMON: Hm.
"Uncle Kimura"?
- Yeah.
- Right. Are you okay? That's...
Oh, yeah. Never shave on a bullet train,
you know what they say.
Well, couldn't hurt to ask, you know?
I'm just gonna keep following him.
Pardon me, "Uncle Kimura."
You guys take care.
Just one thing, though, uh...
Most people assume "suitcase,"
you know, 'cause it's a train,
overnight and all.
But you...
You said "briefcase."
I never said "briefcase."
I think...
I found my Diesel.
- You know what's waiting for us in Kyoto.
- Mm-hm.
We should just get off this train. Now.
If you think I'm stepping off this train
without Lemon or the case,
you must be mistaken.
Okay. Well, the case is
in the first-class lounge.
It's behind the bar.
It's in a trash can. It's yours.
Me, I'm getting off.
I'm gonna go find a temple
and reevaluate my choices or something.
Ooh, that sounds very lovely,
but here's the deal.
I still need a fall guy.
Shit.
- You need a fall guy.
- Yeah.
No, I understand. I get it.
It's a bit of a conundrum,
'cause I'm thinking,
"Do I hand him back in one piece"
or do I chop you up into little pieces
and stuff you inside a fucking Momomon.
That's what's
going through my head right now.
LADYBUG: Hm.
Or...
Or what? You got a better idea, do ya?
You know, before us now is just a wall,
but it's an illusion, man,
it's a construct.
You know,
'cause within that wall sits a window.
A window of opportunity.
Damn it. It's a door.
[TICKING]
Within that wall is a door.
I'm finding it very hard
to follow this story.
My point is, that door is closing.
[LAUGHING]
Now the only question is:
Which one is the Diesel,
which one is the Duck?
"The Duck"?
It's a kid's show.
Thomas the Train Engine.
Close. Thomas the Tank Engine.
Please, mister.
This man, he kidnapped me,
and he said that he's going
to hold me for ransom.
I'm sorry.
I get captivated by white-girl tears.
Bravo.
Common sense tells me that this old,
shaky geezer here is the one in charge,
but I'm really good at reading people
and something tells me
that you are just not fucking right.
So... let's see here.
I mean, I can't shoot you both.
Then I get no answers.
How about this? I'm sure you'll love this.
We're gonna play a little game.
If you wanna play a game,
put both your hands up.
Perfect. I knew you would like this.
You're gonna close your eyes,
and I'm gonna count to three.
Whichever one is in charge,
raise your hand.
Whichever one isn't,
you point at the one who is.
Now if you both raise your hands
or you both point at each other,
I know you're both liars,
and the truth ain't in ya.
And then I'll fucking shoot you both.
Ready?
You said you couldn't kill us both.
You'd get no answers.
- I did say that. Didn't I?
- KIMURA: Yes.
Sometimes you gotta shoot first
and come up with answers later.
One.
PRINCE: Or if I don't answer
this phone when you call...
- Two. Three.
- ...kill Wataru.
[GUNSHOT]
Am I dreaming?
["TOKI NI WA HAHA NO NAI KO NO YO NI
(LIKE A CHILD WITHOUT A MOTHER)" PLAYING]
[KIMURA GROANING]
Sorry, mate. Not your lucky day.
PRINCE: I have a wire in my bag,
and I think that we could use it
to lock the door from the outside.
It was so scary.
He said that if I didn't do what he said,
or if I yelled or anything,
that he would do
awful, awful things to me.
Then why didn't you use this, then?
Yeah, he kidnapped ya
and, uh, gave you his gun to hold, right?
- No, no, no. Um--
- Easy.
Please. I don't know how to use a gun.
I don't know. Please.
Fuck me. You are fucking...
You are really good.
You sure you didn't study?
You're not even afraid
and your lip's quivering.
That's a tear.
That is really authentic, mate.
You're the Diesel.
- I gotta kill ya.
- Please.
I'm just a kid. Please.
How do you do that?!
It's really unbelievable!
Please. Please.
[GROANS]
I got, uh...
It's fucking-- You stay right there.
Did you--? What the fuck is happening?
Everyone loves lemons.
[YELLS]
Fucking die!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm glad you enjoyed the performance.
How did you do that?
I'm not sure.
Just lucky, I guess.
Tell Tangerine... Tell Tangerine...
Tangerine...
He's Gordon.
Tangerine is Gordon.
Getting off this train.
I'm getting that case, and that's it.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Hello?
ELDER: Yuichi. [SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
Uh, it looks like Yuichi lost his phone
on the bullet train.
You can pick it up
at Kyoto Station, though.
- Kyoto?
- There's this Find My Phone app.
- [BEEPING]
- Oh.
Surprisingly accurate.
Bye.
God, he's got a great walk.
LADYBUG: Mr. Wolf.
So you came to kill the Hornet.
[ATTENDANT IN JAPANESE] What happened?
Are you okay?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
Fuck, that thing is hot.
[EERIE PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Momomomo. Momomon. Momon. Momomon.
The pastry chef.
Oh.
You stole my snake, bitch.
That was your--? We should really
call the authorities 'cause someone--
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Take that, punk!
Hey, bitch. One little prick from this,
you know what happens?
- Yes.
- Your blood congeals, clogging your veins.
- You bleed out of your fucking eye socket.
- I said yes!
Weak-ass bitch.
- Stop!
- I'm taking that case.
Give it!
I was promised my money.
- By who?
- Don't know. It was all online.
They said my money was in the case.
What? Someone paid you to have
the kid killed with his own ransom?
Wow. That's dark.
That is dark as-- Stop!
The Hornet stings, bitch!
Lady, you can have the case.
Oh, but you've seen my face, bitch.
Thirty seconds
before the venom does its thing.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GROANS] Oh.
- You bitch.
Oh, shit, man. Do you have a backup?
What do you think, bitch?
[GROANING AND GURGLING]
Oh, shit, man.
You don't have another one?
You gotta be better prepared.
I'm mansplaining,
I'm mansplaining again. I'm sorry.
Uh...
Can I get you something?
You don't seem like a religious person.
Water? Would you like some water?
No?
You want a blanket?
You want me to hold your hand?
Karma is a bitch.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER "I'M FOREVER
BLOWING BUBBLES" PLAYING]
♪ I'm forever blowing bubbles ♪
♪ Pretty bubbles in the air ♪
♪ They fly so high ♪
♪ Nearly reach the sky ♪
♪ Then like my dreams ♪
♪ They fade and die ♪
♪ Fortune's always hiding ♪
♪ I've looked everywhere ♪
♪ I'm forever blowing bubbles ♪
♪ Pretty bubbles in the air ♪
♪ Pretty bubbles ♪
♪ In the air ♪
- [BAG CRINKLING]
- ["SWEET THANG" PLAYING]
MARIA: Talk to me.
It's my bad luck.
It's bad luck on acid.
I gotta get off this train.
Do you have the case?
Yes.
Are you lying on the ground
in the fetal position?
I'm not on the ground.
You need to get up.
- How do you always know what I'm doing?
- Because I know you.
I could journal. I should journal.
Ladybug. Ladybug. Breathe. Deep breaths.
We're almost there.
You just need to get up.
Right.
♪ Sweet thang ♪
♪ Ooh, baby ♪
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
WHITE DEATH:
You have been lying to me, my friend.
Well, cat's out of the bag now, innit?
You were responsible
for keeping my son safe,
for keeping my money safe.
I don't know a thing or two
about being a parent.
But you know what I would do,
being that it's your son
and your money?
I'd stop crying about your dead wife,
get off your fucking lazy ass,
come here and finish the job yourself.
But as we're having
a bit of a heart-to-heart,
got a couple things to tell ya.
Your son's a complete bellend
and fuckin' deserves
to be bleeding out of his eye sockets.
And as for your case,
I haven't seen it since Tokyo.
And I hope someone's fuckin' found it,
put it all on red
and having a fuckin' wonderful time.
I will meet you at Kyoto Station.
Oh, how wonderful. I can't fucking wait.
I want to look into your eyes
when I kill you and your brother.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
My brother.
FANS SINGING ON TV:
♪ I'm forever blowing bubbles ♪
♪ Pretty bubbles in the air... ♪
ANNOUNCER ON TV: West Ham have taken it!
West Ham 1, Chelsea nil.
Morning rush hour's rolling in
quite nicely.
Uh, what's your plan, mate?
You gonna fuckin' waltz up here
and blow my brains out
in front of the whole
fuckin' carriage of witnesses?
There is no one left on that train.
I know.
I bought every ticket
until the end of the line.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
TANGERINE: Oi.
You.
I know you.
You're that girl, aren't ya?
PRINCE: Oh, my God.
Yeah, I never forget a face, me.
[WHIMPERS] I'm so happy to see you.
Please help me.
Um, there's this man,
and he was holding me hostage.
He was wearing glasses,
and he killed my uncle.
And he also killed
this other man who, I don't know,
he just kept talking about
Thomas the Trains and--
Tank Engine.
Yeah, right. Exactly.
But he killed both of them,
and then he said he was going to get away
with some sort of money. I don't know.
I'm sorry, darling. I beg your pardon.
I don't know who the fuck you are.
I'm just a girl who was supposed
to get off at Nagoya, and then this man--
That was fucking ages ago.
I know, but this man, he just said
that I could be a good backup plan
and that a pretty girl
makes a good hostage.
Well, he ain't wrong there.
But, look, keep your fucking knickers on.
- Please just help me.
- All right. Calm down.
Get off or do what the fuck you like.
You're free to go.
- Thank you.
- It's all right. Go on.
I don't know
what you're doing here anyway.
Huh.
Are you okay?
Diesel.
The absolute fucking worst.
Little shit stirrer.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
See, Lemon...
God rest his soul,
was a don.
And he could read people,
see them for who they really are.
He was right.
There's been a Diesel
running up and down this train,
causing all sorts of fucking havoc.
And it was you the whole fucking time,
you dirty little Diesel!
You made Lemon bleed...
and Lemon never bleeds.
Oh, my God! Mister, please help me!
Please! Please help me! Please!
What the fuck are you doing,
you bellend!
Oh...
[GRUNTS]
What?
Diesel!
You fucking bellend!
You're a Diesel.
What the fuck?
- Um...
- What the fuck?
He said that he was going to kill you
and blame everything on you.
He also said that there's someone
waiting for us at Kyoto Station.
Someone scary, who would hurt me.
No one's gonna hurt you.
It's okay.
We're getting off this train.
We make the next stop, we'll be fine.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, kid, come o--
Kid, come on!
I can't, my backpack is stuck!
What?
Leave it, let's go.
- We gotta go, we gotta go.
- No, I can't!
Right now, young lady!
- No!
- It's our last chance!
Please come back!
Kid, please.
I'm scared,
I don't want to be alone, please!
I got it.
It's not your fault, kid.
It's my luck, not yours.
You got your whole life ahead of you.
Make sure you do something
that brings you peace.
'Cause everything else
is a pain in the ass.
And if you run into a guy named Carver,
he's a dick.
You can tell him I said so.
Um...
I, uh...
I took this. I didn't want to leave it.
The man had it,
and I thought you could probably use it
to kill whoever's waiting
for us at the end of the line.
You're not going to let me get hurt.
Be honest.
[IN JAPANESE] Who's there with you?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Really?
Right. Uh...
Okay, fella, you're creepin' me out.
So, if you don't mind,
could you just find another seat, like,
way, way, way down there?
And that way,
I won't have to tell you twice.
[IN ENGLISH] No.
You won't.
[SIGHS] Let's just move.
Let me grab your bag.
Ow. [SCREAMING]
Was that a snake?
Would you know where my son is?
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Oh, fuck.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
PRINCE: Wow.
After everything.
You are the person
who pushed my grandson
off the department store roof.
Why?
Your son.
He was going to help me
kill the White Death at Kyoto Station.
And that was the only way
to get him on this train.
The White Death.
That's right.
But he couldn't even do that.
So he's dead.
Just a few cars back.
They are both dead.
My grandson was pushed off a roof.
What makes you think
I would leave him unprotected?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
My grandson is safe.
And my son is not dead.
Listen, old man--
The only thing you know
about an old man, young lady,
is that he has survived much more,
and much worse, than you.
I'll fucking kill him myself.
- Are you all right?
- From that?
You're not gonna believe
this coincidence
but I already got a dose of antivenom
in me today, so I'm good.
Probably.
The girl...
Her intentions with you
were not honorable.
Yeah.
A blind man could see
you are the one in the dark.
I don't know about a blind man.
She was pretty convincing.
- What did you do to her?
- I did not need to do anything.
- Fate will do what it wills.
- [SCOFFS, THEN LAUGHS]
Why do you laugh at fate?
Man, fate for me
is just another word for bad luck.
And that follows me around like...
I don't know, something witty.
My handler calls me Ladybug.
She's witty.
Ladybug?
Yeah.
This is very lucky, indeed.
No, she's being ironic, she--
Ah, never mind.
I'm going to tell you a story now.
- No, I'm good.
- It's short.
Really, I'm fine.
No, it's very quick.
No, no.
It's a good story for you, I think.
I'm cool.
Here we go.
A long time ago,
I made a promise to myself
that I would provide for my family
no matter what it cost.
I had risen to a highly coveted position
within the Minegishi crime family.
A man raised up to take my place.
A man from the North.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I asked Minegishi not to trust this man.
Minegishi told me I had lost my appetite.
He was not wrong.
But neither was I.
I returned home
and found nothing except ash and blood.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
The White Death
had taken everything from me.
Almost.
[CHILD COUGHING]
Yuichi!
Yuichi.
I went into hiding.
I searched for a way
to strike at the White Death
without endangering what I had left.
But he remained forever out of reach.
I did not think
fate would ever give me
a chance to make things right.
Do you know what they call
a ladybug in Japan?
Uh-uh.
Tentoumushi.
As a boy, I was told
there is a spot on its back
for each
of the seven sorrows of the world.
You see, tentoumushi is not lucky.
It holds all the bad luck
so that others may live in peace.
I don't wanna hold the seven sorrows.
Everything that's ever happened to you
has led you here.
Fate.
Well, that's a shit deal.
At Kyoto Station,
the White Death
will arrive on this train.
I will finally be allowed
to make things right.
My son is a few cars up.
If you could escort him off this train...
Yeah, I don't see the White Death
letting any of us off this train.
You let me worry
about the White Death.
Okay.
Mr. Ladybug?
- Your briefcase.
- Thank you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[KIMURA GROANING]
[IN JAPANESE] Father.
I don't understand.
[IN JAPANESE] It is fate, my son.
And Wataru?
He is safe.
Well...
he seemed like a decent guy.
[IN ENGLISH] He shot me.
Me, too.
Twice.
Still, he had another side to him--
[YAWNING]
Wow.
Oh, man.
Am I in hell?
Ah, fuck.
Fuckin' vest, man.
Oh, you drank the water.
Where the fuck is my brother?
["FIVE HUNDRED MILES" PLAYING]
♪ If you missed the train I'm on ♪
♪ You will know that I am gone ♪
♪ You can hear ♪
Aw, man.
♪ The whistle blow a hundred miles ♪
♪ A hundred miles, a hundred miles ♪
You...
♪ You can hear the whistle blow ♪
You were more
like Thomas anyway, right?
♪ A hundred miles ♪
[YELLS]
♪ Lord, I'm one, Lord, I'm two ♪
♪ Lord, I'm three, Lord, I'm four ♪
♪ Lord, I'm five hundred miles ♪
♪ From my home... ♪
LADYBUG: Fellas.
We need to come up with a plan.
You killed my brother.
You killed my brother, you piece of shit!
Yeah, you fucking shot me!
I'll shoot you in the fucking throat
next time
and your fucking partner Keira Knightley!
- She is not my--
- Hey! Fellas!
When we are so quick to anger,
we are slow to understand.
I'm fast to kick your ass, though,
I swear to God.
Fucking piece of shit! I shoulda
put a bullet through your fucking ass!
When you point a finger
at someone in blame,
there are four fingers
pointing back at you.
Or three. That's weird.
Fuck it! That's it!
You know what I could do!
- We before me!
- You before fucking God--
Gentlemen!
Get off me!
A plum does not resent the hungry man,
but the farmer who planted the tree.
He resents the farmer?
So how do plums have fuckin' resentments?
So how can it resent?
Listen. The White Death is the farmer.
So we're the plums. We're the plums?
It don't make sense.
Why are you motherfuckers using metaphors?
Look, he shot my fucking brother!
You shot my son!
We prepare together...
or we die alone.
That's all I was trying to say.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
ELDER: The white Death waits for you
with his army of assassins.
Killers from all countries.
But he has no idea
my son and I are on this train.
If fate wills,
I will get my revenge.
KIMURA: I'll head to the back
and stop as many as I can.
LEMON: I'll go to the driver car
and get us the fuck out of here.
What are you gonna do, Joburg?
I'm gonna buy us some time.
[DRAMATIC ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[IN RUSSIAN] Daughter.
[IN RUSSIAN] Father.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[FAINT BEEPING]
LADYBUG: Hey, uh, fellas,
I'm looking for a Mr. Death.
Got his case here.
Hey, easy.
Hurt people hurt people.
[IN ENGLISH] I came to see you.
Hm.
And to make you finally see me.
[IN RUSSIAN] The real me.
Hm.
I built myself up
from the nothing you gave me.
All so I could be
the one in front of you today...
my finger on the trigger.
I was the one...
...who deserved your attention.
Your love.
I'm more like you
than that little fuckup ever was.
[LAUGHS]
[IN ENGLISH] Do it.
I came here to kill you.
So kill me.
Kill me like you did
all the others who tried the same.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Do it.
Fucking do it!
- [IMITATES GUNSHOT]
- [GASPS]
Pow. [LAUGHS]
[IN ENGLISH] I see you, dochka.
[IN RUSSIAN] I always have.
But you have never been part of my plan.
We found the American!
[IN ENGLISH] What about the others?
They're all dead.
Uh, good news is I have your case.
Ay, good news, good news.
[IN RUSSIAN] Check the case.
Hurry. Move. Let's go.
WHITE DEATH: Clear the train.
All right, Thomas.
Time for you to start up--
Oh, shit. Everything's in Japanese.
There is no episode in Japanese.
What the f--?
Get on the ground!
Man, I got a bad feeling about this.
We have no idea what's in this case.
What are you talkin' about?
Why is it always gotta be us
that opens this shit?
Just open the goddamn case.
I'd like to keep my fuckin' arms.
Uh, Mr. Death, if I may?
The shadow buyer
who bought all our contracts,
got us all on this train.
Me, the Hornet,
Tangerine, Lemon...
[BOTH] Oh!
That was you, right?
[IN ENGLISH] Yes, very astute.
I brought you on this train
hoping you'd kill each other.
Okay. Well, um...
if I could... Why?
Why you do what you do?
You know, I've been
asking that very question.
If it's so safe,
why didn't he just open it?
What if it's a bomb
and it blows up in our faces?
You think these stupid masks
are gonna protect us?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELDER IN JAPANESE]
All these years later...
the burden of your betrayal
still heavy upon your heads.
Let me relieve you of both.
My wife...
was taken from me.
I heard. I'm so sorry for your loss.
It was a horrible accident.
- Horrible.
- Oh, no.
No. Nothing in life is an accident.
It was an assassination attempt on me.
But fate...
Fate put two wet work operatives,
twins, on a job in Bolivia,
butchering my entire crew.
And I had to go deal with it.
And he didn't hire
two random operators, Lemon.
No, he asked for the two
responsible for the Bolivia job.
That is why it was my wife
in the car that night,
not me.
Fate put my wife in the hospital.
A piece of her rib
piercing her heart.
Only the most skilled cardiovascular
surgeon could save her life.
But two nights earlier,
this surgeon was poisoned.
[YELLING] Oh, my God!
- Fate. Fate again.
- [EKG FLATLINES]
They said my money was in the case!
Don't wanna sound judgmental,
but if you hired the Hornet,
you had your own kid killed?
- Oh, yes.
- Okay.
Oh, yes, I did. The piece of shit.
Please, please.
That night...
- Please pick me up.
- ...I told her not to leave.
To wait for me.
But she promised it was the last time
we would ever bail him out of trouble.
I will come. I will always come for you.
Well, I suppose she was right.
If I had amputated that weakness
out of my life years ago,
she would still be by my side!
Yeah, it helps to process this.
I have a good therapist.
I loved my wife very much.
She taught me a valuable lesson.
If you do not control your fate...
it will control you.
Hm. Hm?
So I took control.
I brought them all here to die.
But now there is only one left.
Mr. Carver.
Whoa. Uh...
Excuse me?
I'm filling in for Carver?
Calling in sick?
Fuck Carver.
The man who murdered my wife.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Bro.
- Just open it!
- Fine. Ya happy?
I'm not Carver!
He went that way.
[GROANING]
Oh, shit. Okay.
Oh, shit. Something's happening.
["HOLDING OUT FOR A HERO" PLAYING]
[YELLING]
Excuse me.
Yep.
[WHITE DEATH IN JAPANESE] Kimura.
Why are you here?
[IN JAPANESE] Your daughter.
It would seem she pushed...
the wrong grandson off a roof.
[IN ENGLISH] Ah, children. You do
the best you can to raise them right.
Cockroach,
I do not know why you are here,
but move out of my way
or you will join your wife.
Our paths were destined
to return to each other.
Okay.
Wait. Fuckin' slow down, mate. Come on!
Hey, so far so good.
You can stop the train.
About that. I took the velocity
of the train and divided it by the mass,
and I realized that I don't know how
to fuckin' drive a bullet train.
Dude, all you do is talk about trains.
Thomas is a metaphor for life,
not how to actually drive--
Get down!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Shit.
I got this! Stop the train!
What?!
English, English, English, English.
English. Brakes!
We're good! I got it!
No!
- Hold on!
- We're on the wrong track!
- LEMON: Oi, Joburg!
- What?
I'm sorry I shot you!
Actually it was, like, twice!
Oh.
Sorry?
You shot me twice!
I'm sorry I shot you twice.
Thanks, man!
That shows real growth!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck.
You are not ruled by strength.
You are ruled by fear!
Fear of the one thing
deep down you cannot control!
Fear of fate!
Hey, and I'm sorry about Tangerine.
Yeah.
But I got another brother now.
Really?
Fuck no!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
For old times' sake.
Fuck it.
["SUKIYAKI" PLAYING]
$#%*
B-20.
Let's go.
- Oh, mate.
- Yeah?
I wanted bubble milk tea.
How about a Wagon Wheel?
[IN JAPANESE] A father...
protects his family.
[LADYBUG YELLS]
[SQUEAKING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
Huh.
[GROANS]
Oh, fuck.
About your wife,
I had nothing to do with that.
It's a mistake.
I'm not Carver.
I only do snatch-and-grab jobs.
The Carver! I want the Carver!
I hired the Carver!
No, he had a stomach thing, man.
I'm just filling in.
You're filling in.
For what it's worth, Carver is a dick.
The most cunning assassin...?
Maybe the laziest.
[GUN CLICKING]
LADYBUG: Aw, come on.
Just let it go, bro.
Do not call me "bro"!
Okay.
Oh...
Ugh.
Dude, did you see that?
What was that?
Dude.
[IN JAPANESE] It's done.
Hey, about this plum. Shouldn't the plum
give up all resentment? Like--
[MACHINE GUN FIRING]
Oh, my God.
It's my luck that delivered
my father's corpse at my feet.
The narcissism on this chick.
Untreatable.
Now I am--
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
What?
What is with this fucked-up family?
You need some suggested reading,
if I may.
Surviving Borderline Personality Disorder.
What?
I highly recommend it.
Now I am the White D--
LADYBUG: What was that?
Was that karma?
Farewell, tentoumushi.
Tangerine.
[SIRENS WAILING]
Wow.
Maria?
Take the gun.
Oh, my God, did you just say "whack"?
We're almost there.
You just need to get up.
Did you come to rescue me?
Did you need rescuing?
You came to rescue me.
Please don't make me regret it.
Okay, don't. Don't. What's happening
to your face? Are you crying?
It's a lot to process.
I want you to know, you are the greatest,
most wonderful handler
that I could ever have. Ever. Ever.
Hm. Do you think maybe
there was a little head trauma?
- Maybe.
- Little bit, yeah.
- A little lightheaded.
- Yeah. Need a banana?
- Potassium might be good.
- Have one in the car.
Hey.
Next time, take the gun.
Don't listen to Barry.
Okay? Simple.
Stop it.
- [SHUSHING] Stop.
- You know,
- I think you were right about one thing.
- Usually am. Come on.
Maybe it is just about how we frame it.
Like, maybe there's no bad luck
or good luck.
Maybe we're all just agents of fate.
Ooh!
- Nice car.
- Yes, it is.
Try not to bleed on it.
Holy mol-- Oh.
Well...
How do you know it's a bad thing?
Huh?
Really?
- See what I'm doing?
- I do.
- Turning that upside down.
This is working.
- [CAR ALARM CHIRPING]
- Yeah.
["I JUST WANT TO CELEBRATE" PLAYING]
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
Wasabi peas.
Fate obviously didn't want me
to have that banana.
Fate did not want us
to get in that car.
MARIA: Well, maybe you've
learned something after all.
LADYBUG:
Fate needs me to find a smart toilet.
MARIA: I take that back. Can you hold it?
LADYBUG: I'm ballpointing.
- MARIA: Walk faster.
- Okay. Yeah.
♪ That's why I'm telling you
I just want to celebrate, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Another day of living, yeah ♪
♪ I just want to celebrate
Another day of life ♪
♪ Had my hand on a dollar bill
And the dollar bill flew away ♪
♪ But the sun is shining down on me
And it's here to stay... ♪
I'm alive! I'm ali--
Oh, fuck me. Fuck me.
Come on, you fucker.
Fuck you!
Stop! Fucking stop!
Tangerines.
Fuck Diesels.
- I am the White D--
- LEMON: Fuck you, Diesel bitch!
Final curtain, huh? Final curtain!
Take a fucking bow!
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I just want to celebrate
Another day of livin' ♪
♪ I just want to celebrate ♪
♪ Another day of life ♪
♪ I wanna celebrate ♪
♪ I just want to celebrate ♪
["KILL ME PRETTY" PLAYING]
♪ Kill me
Kiil me, kill me pretty ♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]