Illumination!
Yeah! illumination!
Whoo!
(WHIMPERING)
Huh?
Oh, man.
Aw. (CONSOLING)
Hmm. Wow.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
NARRATOR: Past the place
that you come from,
far beyond what you've seen,
is a town like your town
if your town was a dream.
Only it's not a dream
or a hoax or a ruse.
BARTHOLOMEW:
Morning!
NARRATOR: It is Christmas
in Who-ville,
the home of the Whos.
Fresh peppermint bread.
Oh, hey, Marge.
Morning, Fred.
(SNIFFS)
Smells like Christmas.
(CAT MEOWS)
(REINDEER BELLOWS)
Whoa!
Where are you going?
Hey, Tom.
Good to see you, Ted.
(DOGS BARKING)
Wreath Man, Wreath Man!
Here you go, kid, have a wreath.
Oh, cool!
BARTHOLOMEW:
Merry Christmas to you.
(LAUGHS)
Have a great day, dear.
You too, hon. See you tonight!
MAN: Hurry up!
Okay!
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
(GROANS)
NARRATOR: Yes, Who-ville is
great, that is known far and wide
and three weeks through December,
this place hits its stride.
(LIVELY CHATTER)
(DOG BARKING)
(MOUSE SQUEAKING)
NARRATOR: Yes, the Whos down in
Who-ville liked Christmas a lot.
But the Grinch,
in his cave north of Who-ville,
did not.
(SNORING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(UPBEAT CHRISTMAS MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
Hmm? (GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(SPANISH CHRISTMAS
MUSIC PLAYING)
(RAP CHRISTMAS
(CHRISTMAS CAROL PLAYING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(CRASHES)
Hmm.
(CHRISTMAS CAROL CONTINUES)
(SIGHS)
Max!
(MAN SINGING)
GRINCH: Max!
GRINCH: Ooh!
I am starving.
Huh?
Max, what is this
depressing bean?
(BARKS)
No, no, no.
That's impossible.
We can't be out of food.
Wha...
Where's my personal reserve
of moose juice? And goose juice?
My emergency stash of Who Hash?
And my secret slew
of frozen Beezle-Nut stew?
(SIGHS)
I specifically bought enough
food to last until January.
How much emotional eating
have I been doing?
(CHOMPING)
(WHINES)
No, I won't. I will not.
I am not going
to Who-ville during...
(HACKING)
Christmas!
(GASPS)
Ugh!
(WHINES)
Fine.
But I'm gonna despise
every second of it.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(SIGHS)
Come on, Max.
NARRATOR: Yes,
the Grinch hated Christmas,
the whole Christmas season.
Now, please don't ask why.
No one quite knows the reason.
It could be his head wasn't screwed
on just right. (NECK CRACKS)
It could be, perhaps,
that his shoes were too tight. (GRUNTS)
But I think the most likely
reason of all
may have been that his heart
was two sizes too small.
(HEART BEATING)
GRINCH:
Now, remember, Max,
this is the time of year when the
Whos are at their most deceptive.
You have my full permission
to attack anyone who so much as
says one kind word to us.
Okay, let's go.
(LIVELY CHATTER)
MAN: Good to see you.
How's work?
WOMAN: Hi. Merry Christmas.
DONNA: Wait, wait, wait!
Hold the bus!
Wait, stop. Oh!
Whoa!
Coming through.
Hey!
Wait! Wait! Sam!
Hold the bus!
Oh!
(BRAKES HISSING)
Whoa!
(CRASHES)
Whoo!
(SIGHS)
Sorry, Donna.
That's okay, Sam.
(SIGHS)
Thanks for stopping.
Whoo! (SIGHS)
They've still got you
on the night shift, huh?
Sure do.
Oh, by the way, Cindy-Lou
forgot her hockey stick.
(SNORING)
(CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
(SINGING SOFTLY) Jingle
bells Christmas smells
Hmm.
(GRUNTING)
Oh!
Thanks, mister.
GRINCH: Ha!
Hey!
(CHILD GASPS)
(GRINCH SCATTING)
You're a mean one, mister.
(MUFFLED SHOUTING)
(GRINCH SCATTING)
It's really such an awful day.
Hey! Merry Christmas.
(GASPS)
Happy holidays, Sue.
SUE: Morning, Fred.
(GROANS)
Season's greetings, folks.
And merry Christmas to you!
Ooh!
(SCREAMING)
(GRINCH CHUCKLES)
(SINGING CHRISTMAS CAROL)
(GROANS)
GRINCH: Huh?
(PANTING, GASPS)
(SCATTING)
(SIGHS)
(ALL SCATTING)
(GROANING)
(GRINCH SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(SINGING CONTINUES)
(GRINCH SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS)
Oh, hello! Happy...
Uh-uh!
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(GAGGING)
(RETCHES)
(STRAINING)
Huh. What's this?
Excuse me?
Are you getting that?
I need it for my Christmas stuffing.
(GASPS)
Mmm... No.
Well, that's not very nice.
(CHUCKLING)
Oh, sugarplum!
Ugh. No, I can't today.
I have a list of errands a mile long
and the babysitter left
the sink backed up.
No, I'm not complaining.
I'm venting. There's a difference.
Okay. Talk to you later.
I have to get breakfast on the table.
Right after I unclog
this drain again!
Ugh! It's like concrete.
Cindy-Lou.
Sweetheart, come eat.
(GRUNTING)
CINDY-LOU: Coming!
(KETTLE WHISTLING)
(CHILDREN GIGGLING)
Buster, we've talked about this.
Your brother's head is not breakfast.
Bleh!
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS, GASPS)
(SIGHING)
Ugh. (INHALES)
Okay.
You all right, Mom?
Me? Oh, yes. Never better.
(SIGHS)
What'd you put down here,
anyway? A roller skate?
No. Just batter.
Me and Ms. Wilbur made cookies.
Oh, that explains it.
Come have some eggs.
I can't, I got to go
mail something.
But I made the beds
and put away the twins' toys.
Thanks, sweetheart.
You didn't have to do that.
I don't mind. (SNIFFS)
Something's burning.
Just a second, sweetie.
Bean, don't feed your brother
with your feet.
Mom! The toast!
I got it.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
Wait, where are you
going again?
I told you,
to mail a letter.
Okay, but just
come here first.
Mom, I got to go.
(SIGHS)
All right.
Muabh.
Okay. Now you can go.
Thanks, Mom.
Bye, Buster. Bye, Bean.
Don't do anything
I wouldn't do!
Roger that, Mom!
Whoo!
And here goes Cindy-Lou Who,
as she dashes through the snow
with a very important letter.
Oh, no! I'm gonna
miss the mailman!
Short cut! (GRUNTS)
Go, go, go!
Whoo! (EXCLAIMING)
Oh, boy.
Bon appétit!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, no!
Whoo!
(BELLS JINGLING)
(EXCLAIMING)
Watch out!
(GRINCH GROANING)
No! My letter!
Argh! What is wrong with you?
Didn't you see me?
I mean, if that was a sled,
well, I'd be dead.
I'm sorry for bumping into you,
but this is really important.
Have you seen my letter?
(SIGHS)
And that right there, Max,
is the true nature of the Who child.
Just right to "Me, me, me.
"My letter. Me, me, me."
No! You don't understand.
This isn't just a letter,
this is the letter.
Oh, really? Let me guess.
Small child, December 20th,
rabidly searching for a
"really important" lost letter.
Might it be your
list of demands to Santa?
They're not demands.
It's more like a wish.
And what I'm wishing for
is really, really important.
Well then, why send a letter?
I mean, if it's really that important
you should just ask him face-to-face.
Oh, but that's right.
No one's ever seen him.
Mmm, my bad.
Come on, Max,
let's get out of here.
Bye, doggy.
BRICKLEBAUM: (SINGING)
Have a holly, jolly Christmas
It's the best time
of the year
There he is, Max.
The happiest Who alive.
The unbearable Bricklebaum.
(CHUCKLES)
He thinks we're friends.
Quick, let's make a run for it.
{ don't know
if there'll be snow
What... What was that?
No.
But have a cup of cheer
(GRUNTING)
Say hello to friends
you know
And everyone you meet
(CHRISTMAS CAROL
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Oh, my goodness, Mr. Grinch!
I'm coming.
Leave Mr. Grinch alone.
That's one tough balloon
that you're fighting there,
you old feisty frosty. Here,
come on. Let me help you up.
I do not want,
or need, your help.
Oh. "Hair dye.
"Gorgeous Green Goddess."
(CHUCKLES)
Oh. How did that
get in there?
Hey, I'm sorry
if I made you uncomfy.
We all got to keep
the gray away. (LAUGHS)
I myself use Chocolate Explosion.
You know what?
If you want to apologize for
something, apologize for that!
My eyes are burning.
Don't blame me.
Haven't you heard?
The mayor wants Christmas to be
three times bigger this year.
That means three times the lights,
three times the eggnog, three times the...
Information needed.
Ha-ha! That's a good one.
Oh, I get it.
This is one of your kidding things.
Finally, something you said
is actually funny. (LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS) Yeah, I do kid a lot,
but, no, this is actually...
Christmas three times bigger!
Well, you're just gonna have a
good time with this, aren't you?
I got to say, it's really nice
to see you laughing.
Sorry, I can't hear you.
I don't speak ridiculous.
Oh, you're a scream!
Have a nice life. Goodbye.
I'll see you later.
Whoo! Oh, man.
Mr. Grinch. Oh.
(CLINKING)
(MAX BARKS SOFTLY)
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(LIVELY CHATTER)
NARRATOR: From the edge of
his ledge way up in the sky
the Grinch felt upset,
though he wasn't sure why.
It could've been Christmas,
all that joy and the such
or some thoughts from his past
that he just couldn't quite touch.
But whatever it was,
it made his heart moan. (SIGHS)
Though he was used to it now,
this being alone.
And now safe in his cave,
and apart from the fray,
he reminded himself...
(SIGHS)
It is better this way.
(MAX WHINES)
That's right, yeah.
Just right there.
No. No.
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Whoa! (GRUNTS)
Cindy-Lou!
Don't worry, Mom!
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
I'm wearing four ski jackets.
Four jackets?
Aren't you a little hot?
(GRUNTS) Yep.
Sweating a little bit.
Are you going somewhere?
North Pole.
Oh, wow!
Any, uh, particular reason?
I got to talk to Santa.
Santa, huh?
Yeah. It's really important.
Well, it must be if you need
to go see him in person.
It sure is.
Okay, then. Well, good luck
and I guess I'll see you
in about a month.
Wait.
It takes a whole month
to get to the North Pole?
Oh, yeah. At least.
Christmas will be over
by the time I got there.
Ah, that's true.
Now, we would miss you
at Christmas.
Wow, I guess I'm gonna have
to come up with another plan.
Hey, maybe while you're thinking,
you could put the halo on the angel.
Okay.
(CHILDREN GIGGLING)
You wanna take your jackets off?
Yeah, at least
one or two of them.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
DONNA: No, boys. Don't pull
the angel's wings off.
She needs those.
(CLOCK GONGS)
(CHRISTMAS CAROL PLAYING)
So, uh...
What do you wanna do today?
(WHINES)
(UPBEAT SONG PLAYING)
(HORN HONKING)
No idea, huh?
Ooh, I got one.
(ORGAN PLAYING SOMBER MUSIC)
(CYMBAL CRASHES)
(ORGAN PLAYING)
(WHINES)
(GRUNTS)
All right, all right.
I'm sorry.
You're a good dog.
(SCOFFS)
But a bad drummer.
What would you like to do?
More than embarrassing
to be beaten by a dog.
(TOY SQUEAKS)
Oh, what's that?
(BARKS)
And checkmate! Again.
(RUMBLING)
What in the world is happening?
(GASPS)
What is that?
It's the most beautiful Christmas
tree you've ever seen. (LAUGHS)
Three times bigger?
That's a hundred times bigger!
Oh, you just wait
till we light it tonight.
It'll sparkle so bright
you'll be celebrating Christmas
with the rest of us. Ho-ho!
(GROANS)
BRICKLEBAUM:
Oh, man! I can't wait.
I'm gonna keep at it.
No!
I'll see you later, Grinchy!
You will not see me later,
and I will not be celebrating.
And that tree,
that tree
has got to go.
Come on, Mom.
Cindy-Lou, look over there.
Wow! That's amazing!
Thank you!
(GROWLING)
Ooh, a three-eyed sock monster!
Awesome robot!
MAYOR McGERKLE: Oh,
how marvelous this time of year is.
Welcome, Who-ville,
to the annual tree-lighting ceremony.
How spectacular
are these ornaments?
Look what I made, everybody.
It's a Christmas dragon.
It came to me in a dream.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, man!
Hey, Bartholomew!
Hey there, Ms. Who.
Here you go!
Got it!
Find a good spot for it.
There it goes.
MAYOR McGERKLE: Now, let's get ready to
flip that switch and light up the sky.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, no!
Not on my watch, you don't.
See you guys soon!
I'm gonna go find Groopert.
Okay. Have fun. Bye. Say bye.
Here you go. I hope your big
brother gets what he deserves.
Hey, Groopert,
how's business?
Good. What I can't sell
I can always eat.
I need to talk to you about
something really important.
Okay.
Come on. Let's go.
All right,
check this out, Groopert.
I'm gonna stay up on Christmas Eve
this year and meet Santa Claus.
Whoa, that is crazy!
Yeah, I really got to
talk to him.
About what?
Well, it's really personal.
But I'm going to tell you
because you're my best friend.
It's about my mom.
She works all night
and takes care of us all day.
And it just isn't fair.
She acts like she's fine,
but I know
it's really hard for her.
So I figured if anyone
could fix that, it'd be Santa.
Wow.
And I just asked him
for a turtle.
MAYOR McGERKLE: Here we go!
Oh, it's starting.
Okay, Who-ville, it is time
to light this beautiful tree.
...17, 18, 19 and 20.
(CHUCKLING)
Okay, lock and load.
All right,
just attach this here
and we'll be ready to launch.
(GRUNTS)
(WHINES, BARKING)
I know! I wish I could see
the look on their faces.
Whoa! (EXCLAIMING)
(SHOUTING) Whoa!
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
Okay. Oh, boy!
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF) Wow.
That could be so much worse.
(SCREAMING)
Let's begin the countdown.
ALL: Ten,
nine,
eight, seven,
six, five,
four, three, two...
Hey! My dragon can fly!
...one!
(ALL CHEERING)
Oh, my!
No, no, no!
No, no!
Whoa!
Wow!
Oh, it's beautiful.
There it is, the most beautiful
tree Who-ville has ever seen.
(PANTING) No! No!
(EXCLAIMING)
(SHOUTING)
(GROANS) No!
No, no.
NARRATOR: He walked through the
crowd and the sound, and the lights.
And his ears heard the thump
of their joy and delights.
And it took him right back
to his earliest years,
to that lost, lonely boy
who cried all of those tears.
That lost, lonely boy,
isolated and sad
with no home of his own,
no mom and no dad.
(GASPING)
And as the Grinch looked
around, he felt downright scared
as he remembered that Christmas
where nobody cared.
Where nobody showed,
not even a flea,
and there were no cards,
no gifts, and no tree.
(LIVELY CHATTER, LAUGHTER)
And as he watched other kids,
one thing became clear,
that this was the single
worst day of the year.
And now here it was,
that day once again
when he felt all those feelings
he felt way back when.
When he'd watch Whos young
and old all sit down to feast,
and they'd feast,
and they'd feast, feast,
feast, feast.
They'd feast on Who-pudding,
and rare Who roast beast.
Which is something the Grinch
could not stand in the least.
And then they'd do something
he liked least of all.
Every Who down in Who-ville,
the tall and the small,
would stand close together
with Christmas bells ringing.
They'd stand hand-in-hand and
the Whos would start singing.
They'll sing, and they'll sing,
and they'll sing,
sing, sing, sing.
NARRATOR: Yes, he couldn't
recall without feeling the sting.
So the Grinch
finally declared...
(WHISPERS)
I must stop this whole thing.
Why?
For 53 years
I've put up with it.
Now...
I must stop this Christmas
from coming,
but how?
(ORGAN JARRING)
(WHINES)
(ORGAN PLAYS NOTE)
NARRATOR:
Then he got an idea,
an awful idea.
The Grinch got
a wonderful, awful idea.
I know just what to do.
I'm going to
steal their Christmas.
(ORGAN PLAYING)
All the trimmings.
All the trappings.
All their gifts and garlands.
When they wake
and see it's gone
then all their joy and happiness
will be gone as well.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
So prepare yourself, Max.
For, tomorrow we begin.
(ECHOING)
(BELL RINGING)
(YAWNS)
(BARKS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTING)
Genius starts
with the abs, Max.
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
It's go time.
And now,
the question we have
all been waiting for.
How will I steal Christmas?
Well, prepare to have your
little doggy mind blown. Poof.
(PANTING)
(CREAKING)
Ta-dal
(CHUCKLES) That's right.
I become Santa Claus.
But instead of giving
all the joy and happiness,
I'll take it away.
If he can deliver Christmas
to the whole world in one night,
then I can certainly steal it
from little old Who-ville.
I mean, come on,
what's Santa have that I don't?
(BARKS)
That's hurtful.
(GRUNTS)
Um, what are you doing
with my bowling ball?
Chasing it.
And you're taking it where?
It's a secret.
(SIGHS) All right,
but not without breakfast. Catch.
Whoa, waffles, my favorite!
Thanks! See you guys later!
(GRUNTS) Here we go.
Hey, Cindy-Lou!
Oh, hey there, Mr. Cubbins.
(CAWING)
(HOOTING)
(GRUNTING)
Ready.
All right. Let's go.
(EXCLAIMING)
Hold on!
BOTH: Whoo!
Yeah!
Let's go, let's go.
Let's move.
(GRUNTING)
Hang on! Whoo!
And dismount.
(SQUIRTING)
So, what do we know?
Waffles are delicious.
Super delicious.
But I meant about meeting Santa.
We know
no one's ever done it.
Hmm...
Okay. How about this?
I'm gonna sit in the living room
with my eyes wide open, like this,
and if I start to drift off,
I'll just open them wider!
I'm pretty sure
you're gonna fall asleep.
And by the time
you wake up...
He'll be gone.
(WHOOSHES)
Nothing but cookie crumbs.
Yeah, you're right.
I got it.
Tell mel
Maple syrup.
All right, maple syrup.
We pour it on the roof,
the reindeer get stuck
and then they can't fly away.
Science!
Won't the syrup just freeze?
Good point.
Also, how do we get all that
syrup on the roof?
Yeah, I got nothing.
(BOTH SIGH)
Wait a minute.
I think I got it.
What?
We're gonna need the whole gang
for this one.
Okay. If I'm gonna become Santa,
then I need to get into character.
All right. Let's see.
"Christmas tree,
"Christmas traditions,
Christmas pudding.”
How does pudding
work its way into everything?
Where is the Santa stuff?
Look at this, little girls and
boys giggling over sugarplums.
Oh.
Look how they did the roof of the
gingerbread house with vanilla icing.
Hmm. Little family of gumdrops.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Huh. So dumb.
So, so stupidly dumb.
Ah, here we are!
"The Legend of Santa Claus.
"Red suit, white beard.
"Always in a jolly mood."
Oh.
That's not gonna happen.
Oh, well. Let's just start by
finding ourselves some reindeer.
(YIPS)
(DEEP SIGH)
Beautiful, isn't it, Max?
This, my little friend,
is the Rein-Horn.
It perfectly recreates
the mating call of the reindeer.
Behold.
(REIN-HORN BLOWING)
(BLEATING)
Oh. Hey, there. Sorry, little goat.
I was calling for a...
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
What was that?
Scram! Skedaddle!
Strange goat.
(BLEATS)
Now, reindeer migrate,
so maybe we'll catch a few
headed south for the winter.
I also read that they tend to
mate in densely wooded...
Will you stop following us?
(BLEATS)
Shoo! Away!
Go back to the goat farm!
Go eat a can.
(SIGHS)
(BLEATS SADLY)
All right, now that that's over,
back to the task at hand. (WIND WHOOSHING)
Whoo. It's a little crisp.
Oh, it's getting really cold.
Oh, goodness!
Can't feel my lips!
Can't blink.
Eyes frozen!
(GASPS)
Max,
we've hit the mother lode.
(GASPS) We'll have
100 reindeer to pull our...
(SCREAMING)
(REINDEER BELLOWING)
(BLEATING)
(SIGHS)
(REINDEER BELLOWS)
Huh?
Well, Santa had eight.
He looks like
he ate the other seven.
Watch and learn, Max.
All right.
(GASPS)
(SNIFFING)
(SCREAMING)
(BELLOWING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(LAUGHS)
(GRINCH GROANING)
(REINDEER GRUNTING)
(GRINCH EXCLAIMING)
Frozen, stinking...
Stop, stop.
Onward, my furry friends.
We're walking toward destiny.
(CROWD CHEERING)
All right,
you called, we came.
So what's up?
Yeah, what's the deal?
Thanks for getting here
so fast, guys.
Follow me.
So what's the big secret?
Yeah, I don't have very long.
My parents set the timer.
Dude.
Don't ask. It's new.
All right, everybody,
brace yourselves.
In exactly 48 hours
we're going to do something
that's never been done before.
We're gonna trap Santa Claus!
Trap Santa?
Why would we wanna do that?
Duh. To steal all his toys.
I love it.
That's a great idea.
Not to steal his toys.
To, um...
To talk to him.
What? Why'd you wanna
talk to him?
It's personal.
Yeah, it's kinda personal.
Well, I don't wanna do it
if you won't tell me why.
What are you talking about,
"personal"?
Axl, when you asked to borrow
$16 and my mom's suitcase,
did I ask you why?
No.
(0ZZY CHUCKLES)
And what about you, Ozzy?
Remember when you got stuck in that...
All right, all right,
okay. Jeez.
I did it because
you're my friend.
And when something matters to
you, that means it matters to me.
That's beautiful.
Okay, okay, okay.
You convinced me.
Count me in, too.
All right, we're in.
Great! Now let's do this.
AXL: Yeah, let's do this!
OZZY: Let's make it happen. Awesome.
AXL: Cool. That is so cool.
CINDY-LOU:
To the bikes.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CAT MEOWS)
DONNA: Cindy-Lou, dinner time!
MAN: Come here, guys, dinner time!
WOMAN: Time to eat!
Ooh, dinner.
All right, we meet
first thing in the morning.
Okay- All right-.
See you tomorrow.
See you guys in the morning.
WOMAN: Ozzy, timer!
Okay, Mom!
(SNOW CRUNCHING)
(LOUD CRUNCHING)
(WHISPERING) This is the loudest
snow I've ever heard in my life.
You two, go around the back.
Wait for me to drop the sleigh
from the roof. Okay?
(REINDEER GRUNTS)
Go, team.
(GASPING)
(SNORING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRINCH SHUSHING)
(GASPING)
(GROWLING)
(BARKING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
(BARKING)
(YELPING)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
What? What's going on?
Hey! Who taught Mabel
how to use the doorbell?
Man, that's awesome.
You smart little dog.
(PANTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
ALL: (SINGING) Holy infant
Huh? What's this?
So tender and mild
Sleep in heavenly peace
(SIGHS)
(PANTING)
(REINDEER GRUNTING)
All right, here it comes.
Get ready.
(GROWLING)
(BARKING)
(YELPING)
(SCREAMING)
(DOG HOWLING)
(CHATTERING)
Oh! (LAUGHS)
Oh, look at that.
Mabel is delivering cakes now.
I mean, is this the best
Christmas or what?
(GRINCH YELPING)
(BELLS JINGLING)
Ooh! Holy moly!
Man, I don't know
what's in this cake,
but I think I just saw
Santa Claus. (LAUGHS)
Let me get another piece.
(LAUGHING)
Today was great!
We did mean things
and we did them in style.
(WHINES)
Max,
you know the rules.
You sleep in your bed,
and I sleep in...
(REINDEER GRUNTING)
Oh, no, no, not you, too.
I don't believe this.
Max, did you teach him
puppy eyes?
(WHINES)
(DEEP WHINE)
Fine. This one time.
(SIGHS)
(CREAKING)
(BELLOWING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHING)
(SNIFFING)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(CLATTERING)
(SNIFFING)
(GRUNTS)
(SNORING)
(YAWNING)
(CLATTERING)
(WHINES)
(GRUNTS)
Mmm. Now that is
a great cup of coffee!
(MAX GRUMBLES)
(BELLOWS)
Max, this morning, you and I
need to do some recon.
Fred, you just sit right there.
And don't touch anything!
Intel, Max,
that's what we're after.
How many houses are in Who-ville
and how many Whos?
How many wreaths
and trees and chimney flues?
I'll be in your ear the whole
time, and whatever you're seeing
(THROUGH COMMS)
I'll be seeing on the monitor.
Ready? Now off you go, Max.
(WHINES)
Fly, boy!
Fly!
(BARKS)
Max, stop socializing!
Now, let's go in for a look.
Okay.
Six houses on Oak Street...
Oh, watch out!
What?
Oh.
GRINCH:
Okay. Go, go, go, go!
Now cut through Main Street
and survey the south side.
(LIVELY CHATTER)
Look at those
greedy little gift monsters.
Loading themselves up
with Christmas junk.
Okay, Max, turn right here.
So I woke up this morning,
got dressed, had my coffee,
went outside,
looked on the roof.
My sleigh was gone.
My, my, I wonder who took it.
(GRINCH CHUCKLES)
Huh?
Okay, let's see here.
If we do 28 houses an hour for six
hours, that would be sausages.
(EXCLAIMS) Sausages?
Max! Don't even think about it.
(WHINES)
Max!
Max, are you okay?
Max?
Oh, hey, look, it's me.
Oh, dear. (GROANS)
(GROANS) Bad dog.
Fred! We're home!
Fred!
What are you doing?
Okay.
Come on, we got work to do.
Now, let's plan our route.
First, now, we go south,
quick jaunt to the east,
and then this house,
skip the subdivision for the moment,
knock off the entire
southeast quadrant of the town.
And then we finish it all up
on Whistling Who Lane.
That's 223 houses
and only seven hours
of darkness to work with.
That means we have to be
fast and focused.
And believe you me,
there will be temptation...
(BUZZES)
...all around us.
Behold! The present!
This is our enemy.
You will want to unwrap it
and play with it.
(WHINES)
Hmm. But you must not!
And if you can get past the
present, the only obstacle left is
the cookie.
Look at it in all its red,
sugary splendor.
(SNIFFING, BELLOWS)
No, no, no!
Look at yourselves!
Discipline! We must...
(CHOMPING)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS) Resist.
Are you ready?
GROOPERT: Almost.
Good. Think jolly.
0ZZY: And fat.
GROOPERT:
Okay, I'm ready.
All right, quick.
Everybody hide!
Three, two, one,
cue Santa!
That means you, Groopert.
(EXCLAIMS, GROANS)
(IN MONOTONE) Ho, ho, ho, ho.
Look at this pretty house.
I will leave presents
for the people.
Come on, it's not
the school play, dude.
Then why do I have to
wear the outfit?
Groopert, focus!
Just get the cookie.
But I can see the string.
Stop worrying!
It'll be dark at night.
What if he has a flashlight?
Have you ever seen a picture of
Santa with a flashlight?
No, but I just...
Groopert!
Just pick up the cookie!
Hmm. What do we have here?
A delicious little cookie.
(GROOPERT SHOUTS)
Groopert!
Groopert?
GROOPERT: Uh, hey, guys.
Do I still
get to eat the cookie?
(MAX BARKS)
(FRED GRUNTS)
GRINCH: All right.
So, I tinkered
with our sleigh a bit.
Behold!
(WHIRRING)
Look at this, Max.
Now you'll be riding in style.
A throne for a barking prince.
How do you like that?
(BARKS)
All right, Fred,
you are the engine of this
great machine. Understood?
(LOW GRUNTING)
Good.
Now, remember,
this is just a practice run.
But on this team,
we practice like we play.
So, let's leave it
all out on the snow.
(BELLOWS)
Whoa!
Okay!
All right, how about that?
Now, let's pick up the pace
and see how she handles.
(SHOUTING) Whoo!
Hang on!
No, no, no. No problem!
It's all under control.
Hold on!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Whoa!
(LAUGHING)
We're doing it, Max.
We are doing it!
We will not be...
Stopped?
What happened?
Fred?
Oh. Um...
Sorry, but we don't need
any more reindeer.
No. Go. Get. Shoo.
I have what I need.
(BELLOWING)
(SIGHS)
It's okay, Fred.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(WHINES)
(SIGHS)
On our own again, Max.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
NARRATOR: It was the day before
Christmas and the Whos were abuzz,
all doing the things
that a Christmas Who does.
Some were out buying presents,
others just milled about.
There you go, sir.
But the whole town felt joyous
of that, there was no doubt.
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
The weather was perfect,
and soon snow would fall.
This surely would be...
Everyone ready?
...the best Christmas of all.
(BELL DINGING)
Max! There you are!
Check this out!
Whoa! Ah!
I've been making
lots of cool...
Whoa! (LAUGHS)
Stuff.
Ooh, more coffee!
(SLURPS)
It's gonna be a big night.
We got all the gizmos
and gazmos we need,
but we still don't have
the proper outfit.
Come on, let's do
a little stitching.
(WHIRRING)
There's only one thing
left to do.
Max,
do you know what you are?
You are a sturdy little fella.
And loyal.
Very loyal.
In fact, I think
you're the best dog
a Grinch could hope for.
(WHINES)
And that is why
I'm promoting you.
Max,
you will guide
my sleigh tonight.
(BARKING)
Ha-ha!
I knew you wouldn't
let me down.
NARRATOR: It was now Christmas Eve.
There was joy in the air.
For in just a few hours,
Santa Claus would be there.
And the gifts would be left,
and the stockings all filled.
And the anticipation, well,
it started to build.
WOMAN: Ozzy,
what are you doing?
Trying to get myself tired.
(PANTING)
All right, eight hours
till Christmas morning.
That's 28,800 seconds.
Okay, and sleep!
Waffle One, this is Waffle Two.
Are you there? Over.
CINDY-LOU: / read you
loud and clear, Waffle Two.
GROOPERT:
This is Groopert, by the way.
CINDY-LOU: Yeah, ll got that.
GROOPERT: Oh. ! just wanted to wish
you good luck with Santa Claus.
Thanks. Talk tomorrow.
So, you got any
last-minute wishes for Santa?
Yep. I have
one great big wish.
Good.
Because you deserve
everything you want and more.
Thanks, Mom.
I want the same thing for you.
(SIGHS)
How did I end up with
such a wonderful daughter?
I don't know.
Sometimes you just get lucky.
Well, then I really did.
Me, too.
I love you, Mom.
I love you, sweetheart.
Good night.
NARRATOR: The Grinch was now
ready to start his big trip.
He stood like a captain
aboard a great ship.
Yes, the time had now come
to take off like a shot.
Here we go, Max.
Let's see what you've got!
(BARKING)
What?
Max?
Max, are you okay?
(CREAKS)
Huh?
Yeah, Max! Attaboy!
Go, boy! Go!
(MAX BARKING)
(LAUGHING)
NARRATOR: And down the Grinch
came on his great fateful ride
toward the good homes of Who-ville
and the Christmas inside.
(GRINCH CACKLING)
He had planned it and prepped
it big detail to small.
Yes, he'd get rid of Christmas
now, once and for all.
You take the outside,
I'll take the inside.
House number one.
NARRATOR: He was ready to
pounce, and set the score right.
He'd make up for the past,
and he'd do it tonight.
Okay.
Now let's steal Christmas.
NARRATOR: He swept up their
presents with the speed of a wiz.
And he knew he'd cause sadness,
only theirs now, not his.
(VACUUM WHIRRING)
(CLICKS)
(CHUCKLES EVILLY)
All this excess and nonsense
it was all about greed.
About meaningless stuff
that they didn't even need.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
The Grinch went to work.
He scooped up the toys.
He raced against time,
he raced against joy.
He hit a few snags as he made
his way through... (YOWLING)
...an angry orange cat
and a sleepwalking Who.
(GASPS) Huh?
Thank you, Mommy.
NARRATOR: He stole pop guns and
bicycles, roller skates, drums,
checker boards, tricycles,
popcorn and plums.
Gadgets and gizmos
and dolls with strange names,
goofballs and shloof-balls
and video games.
And he swiped, and he poached.
Yes, the stealing was on.
And this day that he hated,
well, he made it be gone.
This is it. The last house.
(SINGING) Dashing through the
snow in a one-dog open sleigh
(GRUNTING)
One more house to go
and Christmas goes away
(GRUNTS, LAUGHS)
(SCATTING)
Huh?
(SIGHS)
Oh, what the heck.
Huh? (YELPING)
(BELLS CLINKING)
He's here!
What the...
(GROANS, EXCLAIMING)
(GRUNTING)
How do I get out of this?
Santa Claus.
Oh. Hello.
A little help, please.
I'll let you down,
just give me a minute.
Oh, that'd be great.
I'm coming.
Just trying to remember
which cord it is.
(GROANING)
Oh, no!
I'm so sorry, are you okay?
Yeah. I guess so.
Let me help you.
(SIGHS)
Sit down here.
Drink this.
It'll make you feel better.
Uh... Thanks.
Wow. I can't believe
it's really you!
Uh...
Yeah.
I'm so sorry about the trap and
everything, but I really need...
Hey! Why are you
taking our Christmas tree?
(SPITS)
Well...
One of the lights
wasn't working,
so I thought I'd take it back
to the workshop
and see if I could fix it.
I didn't know you did that.
Yeah. Sure.
Now, why don't you go back
upstairs to bed,
and then when you wake up
the tree will be fixed
and your presents
will be waiting under it.
Wait. You don't understand,
I don't want presents.
(CHUCKLES) Of course you do.
Everyone wants presents.
No, no, really, I don't!
I want you to help my mom.
Your mom?
Yeah. She works so hard
and is always doing stuff
for other people,
and I just want her
to be happy.
You want me
to help your mom?
You're Santa.
You make people happy.
And everyone
should be happy, right?
(STAMMERS) Yeah...
I guess they should.
Santa, are you okay?
What? Uh...
Yeah. I'm fine.
(CHUCKLES)
Now, why don't you
go back up to bed, hmm?
Okay.
I wish you could
celebrate with us tomorrow.
We all get together and sing.
It's so beautiful
that if you close your eyes
and listen,
all of your sadness
just goes away.
That sounds nice.
(CHUCKLES)
Huh?
Thank you, Santa.
Good night.
Good... Good night.
(WHINES)
I just met the strangest
little Who girl.
(WHINES)
All right, Max. Let's go.
NARRATOR: He tried to forget it,
but the words filled his head
and he found himself thinking
about what the young girl had said.
It was hard to imagine.
Could it really be true?
But if they could all be happy,
maybe he could be, too.
(YAWNS)
(GASPS)
(GIGGLING)
What?
NARRATOR: Her head felt unsteady,
and her heart was just sick.
Oh, no!
It must be a joke
or a prank, or a trick.
Who would do such a thing?
Who would stoop down this low?
And then one little girl
realized she might just know.
3,000 feet up,
up the side of Mount Crumpit,
the Grinch rode with his load
to the tip-top to dump it.
Keep going.
We're gonna make it.
IZZY: Oh, dear.
What... What happened?
Where's the decorations?
All the presents.
Aw, man!
Mom, it's my fault.
What... What is?
All of this.
I trapped Santa last night
because I wanted to ask him
to do something special for you.
But think I made him mad
and that's why he stole
everyone's Christmas.
No! No, no. No, honey,
this isn't your fault.
He didn't steal Christmas,
he just stole stuff.
Christmas is in here.
And besides, I already have the
greatest gift I could ever get.
You.
(GRUNTING)
Just one more shove.
(SINGING IN DISTANCE)
What's that? Do you hear it?
They're singing?
I don't understand, Max.
Don't they know what I've done?
NARRATOR: As he watched the small
girl, he thought he might melt.
If he did what she did,
would he feel what she felt?
And the luscious sound swelled,
reaching up to the skies.
And the Grinch heard with his
heart, and it tripled in size.
(HEART BEATING)
(GASPING)
(SIGHS)
What? Oh, no!
(SHOUTS)
No! No, no, no!
Oh, no!
(SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
No, don't worry. I got it.
(BARKING)
Max, it's okay. I'm...
(SHOUTS)
(EXCLAIMING)
Oh, no, no, no.
Max!
(GRUNTS) Huh?
(GRUNTING)
(MAX BARKS)
(FRED GRUNTING)
Fred?
(BELLOWING)
(BLEATS)
You...
You came back.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Max, the gifts!
We have to return them. (BARKS)
NARRATOR: And having heard the Whos'
goodness, having felt the Whos' song,
he tried to make right
what he had made wrong.
(TRUMPET PLAYING)
(ALL MURMURING)
Uh...
Hello, everybody.
It was me.
I stole your Christmas.
I stole it because...
Because I thought it would fix
something that happened along time ago.
But it didn't,
and I'm sorry.
I'm so very sorry.
For everything.
(MAX BARKS)
Not now, Max.
I need to be alone.
(BELL RINGING)
(STAMMERS) I kind of
thought you might like it.
You don't like it?
Oh, I could take it back.
It's not a big deal.
I just thought maybe you... (BARKING)
(BARKING)
(TOY SQUEAKING)
Oh, hey. (CHUCKLING)
Merry Christmas
to you, too, Max.
(SQUEAKING)
(LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
That's gonna get old.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
What was that?
Huh?
Uh, hello.
Hi.
Remember me?
Yes. Yes, I do.
I remember you.
My name is Cindy-Lou.
Cindy-Lou Who.
It's nice to meet you,
Cindy-Lou.
Oh, my name is Grinch.
(TOY SQUEAKING)
And, uh, this is Max.
(CHUCKLES) Whoa!
Nice to meet you, Max.
I just came to invite you to
our house for Christmas dinner.
What? Me?
But took your gifts.
Yeah, I know.
And your trees.
Yep.
I stole your whole Christmas.
I know you did.
But we're inviting you anyway.
But why?
Because you've been alone
long enough.
Dinner's at 6:00!
Don't be late.
And make sure you bring your
sweet doggy, too!
(SIGHS)
(SIGHING)
(LIVELY CHATTER)
(CHRISTMAS MUSIC PLAYING)
Right. Okay.
Mmm.
Hmm.
(PANTING)
Um, this is a bad idea.
(STAMMERS) I can't do this.
I can't do this.
They're all gonna hate me.
(SIGHS)
All right. (GRUNTS)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
I did it.
Oh, Mr. Grinch.
I'm so happy
you decided to come.
Welcome!
Thank you for inviting me.
Uh, I wore a tie.
And it's a very nice tie.
Cindy-Lou, look who camel!
Mr. Grinch! You're here!
Hello!
Come on in,
I'll show you around.
Oh. Okay.
(LIVELY CHATTER)
(CHRISTMAS MUSIC PLAYING)
Hello, Mr. Grinch.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas to you, too.
Aunt Ida, I'd like you to meet
my friend, the Grinch.
Oh, it's nice to meet you,
Mr. Grinch.
Thank you.
It's nice to be here.
(GRUNTING)
Oh, here,
let me take that for you.
Oh, thank you.
Cindy-Lou, could you make
a little room for this, please?
No, don't worry.
I've got it.
Oh, isn't that thoughtful?
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
BRICKLEBAUM: Is that grouchy,
grumpy Grinchy I see standing over there?
(LAUGHS)
Bricklebaum, good to see you.
Come on, Grinchy, give me a hug.
Oh! (CHUCKLES)
It don't count if
you don't hug back, buddy.
Okay, come take your seats,
everyone. Dinner's ready.
Come on,
you're sitting next to me.
Here you go.
(SLURPING)
(GASPS)
(LIVELY CHATTER)
This is my first Christmas dinner.
What happens?
You'll see.
Would you do the honors,
Mr. Grinch?
Oh.
Uh, okay.
Do you mind
if I say something first?
Not at all.
Um, well, everybody,
I just want to say,
I've spent my entire life
hating Christmas
and everything about it.
But now I see that
it wasn't Christmas I hated,
it was being alone.
But I'm not alone anymore.
And I have all of you
to thank for it.
But especially
this little girl right here.
Ma'am,
your daughter's kindness
changed my life.
That's my girl.
Oh, that was beautiful.
That's my best friend.
Merry Christmas, Mr. Grinch.
Merry Christmas, Cindy-Lou.
(BARKS)
NARRATOR: And the Grinch raised his
glass, and led the Whos in a toast.
To kindness and love,
the things we need most.
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SNIFFING)
(VACUUM WHIRRING)
(SAW WHIRRING)
(PANTING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(WHIRRING)
(GOATS BLEATING)